al
al
[Music]
[Música]
Ok PE we
Ok PE we
go the Finally here perform it for you
go the Finally here perform it for you
if you know the words you can join him
if you know the words you can join him
to put your hands together if you W Clap
to put your hands Together if you W Clap
as we take you through this monkey rap
as we take you through this monkey rap
[Music]
[Música]
kke
kke
Kong Donkey Kong He's the leader of the
Kong Donkey Kong He's the leader of the
bunch you know him well He's Finally back to
bunch you know him well He's Finally
Kick some ta his Coconut
back to Kick some ta his Coconut
gum ands If he shoots It's gna hurt He's
gum ands If he shoots It's gna hurt He's
bigger faster and stronger too He's the
bigger faster and stronger too He's the
First member of the d
First member of the d
Crew Donkey
Crew Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong
Kong Donkey Kong
iskey
iskey
Kong Donkey Kong is
Kong Donkey Kong is
[Music]
[Música]
Donkey
Donkey
this
this
link si to su her qui and When She needs to be
link si to su her qui and When She needs
She can flo through the air and
to be She can flo through the air and
Climb up tre if you choose
Climb up tre if you choose
her wrong with a skip a H She's
her wrong with a skip a H She's
cool Donkey
cool Donkey
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
Kong Donkey Kong is here
Kong Donkey Kong is here
d Donkey Kong Donkey Kong
d Donkey
is he has no Style he has
Kong Donkey Kong is he has no Style he
no
has no
Grace has a funny Face he can
Grace has a funny Face he can
hand when he needs to and stretch his
hand when he needs to and stretch his
Arms out Just for you inflate himself
Arms out Just for you inflate himself
just like a balloon  this crazy just his
just like a balloon this Crazy justs his
[Music]
[Música]
tunke Kong is here
tunke Kong is here
Donkey
Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong is
Kong Donkey Kong is
[Music] kke Kong
[Música]
He's Back Again and about time to
kke Kong He's Back Again and about time
and this Time He's in the mo he can
to and this Time He's in the mo he can
fly real H with Jet with his pistols out
fly real H with Jet with his pistols out
He's One tough he'll Make You Smile when
He's One tough he'll Make You Smile when
he Plays his Tun butlin bew
he Plays his Tun butlin bew
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Kong Donkey Kong is
Kong Donkey Kong is
here Donkey
here Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong is Finally He's here
Kong Donkey Kong is Finally He's here
for you  It's The Last member of the dk
for you It's The Last member of the dk
Crew this K so strong it isn't funny can makein Cry fory pick up a
Crew this K so strong it isn't funny can
with eas makes crushing
fory pick up a with eas makes crushing
Rocks seem such a breeze he May move
Rocks seem such a breeze he May move
Slow he can't jump High but this One
Slow he can't jump High but this One
Hell Of A Come on cranky take it to the
Hell Of A Come on cranky take it to the
fridge
fridge
Walnut peut pineapple smells grapes
Walnut peut pineapple smells grapes
melons oranges and Coconut shell oh yeah walnuts peanuts
melons oranges and Coconut shell oh yeah
pineapple
walnuts peanuts pineapple
smells melons oranges and Coconut shells
smells melons oranges and Coconut shells
oh yeah walnuts peanuts  pineapple
oh yeah walnuts peanuts pineapple
smells melons oranges and Coconut shell
smells melons oranges and Coconut shell
oh yeah walnuts peut pineapple
oh yeah walnuts peut pineapple
smell Coconut ah
smell Coconut ah
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Sparkle
Sparkle
[Music]
[Música]
Oh ah
Oh ah
w
w
[Music]
[Música]
ye [
ye
he
he
[Music]
[Música]
love k
love k
P
P
[Music]
[Música]
w
w
my vibe got cut off eh I mean
se me ha cortado el rollo eh o sea justo
I was just coming to dance I was just coming to
venía yo a bailar justo venía yo a
dance and and they cut my vibe off you
bailotear y y me han cortado el rollo
know they took off my music eh What's up What's up What's up How are you how are
sab me han quitado la música eh Qué
you since
estáis qué tal estáis desde de la resaca
yesterday's hangover no what a live yesterday Today don't take
de ayer no menudo directo ayer Hoy no me
up so much of my time here eh
vayáis a robar aquí tantísimo tiempo eh
video on the main channel great
vídeo en el canal principal pedazo de
video
vídeo
and live between the salsa great
e directo entre salseo pedazo de
live I don't have much more to tell you
directo poco más tengo que comentaros
about here a
por aquí
little more let's see I'm going to blur I'm not going to
poco más a ver voy a desenfocar no voy a
focus on the background we're not going to change
enfocar el fondo no vamos a cambiar de
cameras over here okay over here over here
cámara por aquí bien por aquí por aquí
okay But anyway I do have two or three salsas
vale Pero bueno dos o tres salseos sí
for you okay I'm
que tengo para ustedes vale estoy
working during the afternoon on
trabajando durante la tarde en una
something very nice that you'll be able to see soon
cosita muy guapa que pronto podréis ver
and it's going to  to like it a lot it's a little surprise it
y os va a gustar mucho es una sorpresita
's a little surprise Javi I'm stubborn
es una sorpresita Javi estoy emperrado
because I got a member in te gossip
porque me tocó miembro en tes salseo
here
aquí
No, well you pay for it, well you pay for it would be a
No pues págalo tú pues págalo tú sería
good idea for you to pay for it no, you don't think you don't
buena idea que lo pagas tú no no crees
think that it's time for
que no crees que que es el momento de
you to
que tú lo
pay for it I say, eh I mean if it's
pagues digo yo eh o sea si no te toca es
not your turn it's because the gift is not for you It's for you to buy it
que no está para ti el regalo Está para
and for you to
que tú te lo compres y para que tú lo
pay for it I say, eh I say,
pagues digo yo eh digo yo
eh And if we give a group kiss we deserve it
eh Y si nos damos un beso grupal nos lo
we deserve it we deserve it
merecemos nos lo merecemos lo merecemos
today we should spend a little time on the
hoy habría que pasarnos un poco por la
community too
comunidad también
eh today we should spend it on the
eh hoy habría que pasarlo por la
community The thing is I don't know if it's on
comunidad Lo que pasa que no sé si va a
time I also would have liked to see
tiempo También me hubiera gustado ver el
Gibel's gossip with Javil Canino but
salseo de gibel con el javil canino pero
Javil Canino The account has been deactivated
javil canino Se Ha desactivado la cuenta
and so no we can't see it we can't
y entonces no no podemos verlo no
see it We also have this
podemos verlo También tenemos este tema
fake issue that she's like very indignant no
fake que está como muy indignada no
because we don't take her
porque no nos tomamos en serio su su
exclusive of let's see me I don't it's that I didn't
exclusiva de a ver yo yo no es que no me
take her exclusive this one seriously about
tomara en serio su exclusiva esta de lo
that auron  He has a girlfriend, what happens is
de que auron tiene novia lo que pasa es
that let's see the evidence was
que la a ver las pruebas eran
a little bit, no, the bracelet
poquillo no de la pulsera
is there, the bracelet matches that photo of
está la pulsera coincide con esa foto de
[Music]
[Música]
Auron In fact, I don't know if it's a bracelet or
auron De hecho no sé si es una pulsera o
a hair tie, okay Yes, here she has the
una goma del pelo vale Sí aquí tiene la
bracelet again, okay, but it wasn't that
pulsera otra vez vale pero tampoco había
much, it wasn't that much,
tanto tampoco había
there's the message from the girl that I
tanto está el mensaje de la chica que yo
considered it As if it wasn't an occasion on
lo consideraba Como no una ocación por
the girl's part to create the
parte de la chica para crear el
content, no, also, no, in the end, this doesn't
contenido no también no al final esto no
hurt her, not seeing how things have gone for her,
le viene mal no viendo como la ha ido
Gemita, let her return the action if she got
gemita que devuelva la acción si le tocó
a gift membership, let him give away
una membresía de regalo que él regale
memberships and we make a
membresías y hacemos una cadena de
membership chain, already Román, already Román, I understand.
membresía ya Román ya Román entiendo Yo
Today, no, no, I'm not going to have the face, no, today, I'm
hoy no no no voy a tener la la cara no
not going to have the face
hoy no voy a tener la cara
to ask you for a membership, no super chat, no
de de pediros ni membresía ni super chat
objectives or anything, today, no, I'm not going to have that, let's not have that
ni objetivos ni nada hoy no no voy a
shameless one, it wouldn't be good, no, let's see what
vergona no estaría bueno no a ver lo que
happens is that if today, today, I'm going to
pasa es que si hoy hoy se lo voy a
recognize it, Fay, no,
reconocer yo a fay no
Auron's cap. Okay, what's up with this
e gorra de auron Vale qué pasa con esta
cap? Well, if I'm not mistaken, I'm going
gorra Pues que si no me equivoco me voy
to get into Auron
a meter en auron
House. Auron
house
House
auron House
if I'm not mistaken this cap still can't be
si no me equivoco esta gorra todavía no
bought let's see
se puede comprar a ver navidades
tasty Christmas Christmas Christmas is tasty
sabrosas Navidad Navidad es sabrosa te
the bastard puts you on the page ge fandom
pone el cabrón en la página ge fandom
accessories cap cap cap yes you can
accesorios gorra gorra gorra sí se puede
buy the cap yes you can buy the
comprar la gorra sí se puede comprar la
cap I put the cap on and yes you can
gorra yo me meto la gorra y sí se puede
buy Add to the sixth embroidered logo
comprar Añadir a la sexta logo bordado
now well Now
ahora bien Ahora
a kiss Cris has given away 50 memberships
un beso Cris ha regalado 50 membresías
El Román you've gotten jealous A kiss
El Román te has puesto celoso Un beso
man Thank you very much Thank you very much
tío Muchísimas gracias Muchísimas
handsome Román has gotten jealous
gracias guapo Román se ha puesto celoso
because he's no longer the protagonist he's no longer the
porque ya no es el prota ya no es el
protagonist of this channel now the channel is
prota de este canal ahora el canal lo
carried by a bunch of Sebastians three or
carrean un montón de Sebastianes tres o
four Sebastians let's see curious that the
cuatro Sebastianes a ver curioso que la
girl puts on the Auron Play cap and
chica se ponga la gorra de auron Play y
puts on the Quevedo and
ponga lo de la canción de Quevedo y
Aitana song no after the fay thread
Aitana no después del hilo de fay
curious to say the least I would have
curioso cuanto menos yo le hubiese
added that the cap still can't be
añadido que la gorra todavía no se puede
bought but it can be bought They
comprar pero sí se puede comprar Es que
had told me today that it couldn't be bought
me habían dicho hoy que no se podía
but it can be bought yes it can be
comprar pero si se puede si se puede
bought the cap is there S it can be no
comprar está ahí la gorra S se puede no
no it's that they had told me no no but be
no es que me habían dicho no no pero
careful because the cap is also a it's a
cuidado que la gorra además es un es una
cap that is not yet is not for
gorra que todavía no está no está a la
sale is going to come out No, I mean, it cannot be bought yet, but yes it can, yes it
venta va a salir No o sea todavía no se
can, there it tells me yes, but let's go, the girl is
puede ahí me sale que sí pero vamos la
following the
chica siguiendo el
joke, the girl is following the
cachondeo la chica está siguiendo el
joke on purpose, no, this girl
cachondeo a propósito no esta chica
was on Juan Guarnizo's team for
estaba en el equipo de Juan guarnizo Por
receiving extra salaries for how, how, this
recibir sobresueldos de cómo cómoo esta
girl was on Juan
chica estaba en el equipo de Juan
Guarnizo's team for receiving extra salaries from esp, she
guarnizo Por recibir sobresueldos de esp
's from Be careful, Oh, that doesn't go down well because she
es de Cuidado Ah que no cae bien ya que
has some stories and some things going on. Let's
tiene ahí unas historias y unas movidas
see, I have no idea because I, the
A ver no tengo ni idea porque yo los
Kill players, you know, it does
temas jugadores de la Kill ya sabéis que
n't
no
say Maribel Javi, today I'm lost.
dice Maribel Javi hoy estoy perdida
Who is the girl? Well, she's a player
Quién es la chica pues es una jugadora
from one of the soccer teams on the
de uno de los equipos de fútbol de la
King list, okay, what team?
King list vale De qué equipo Pues de
Well, from
pues del equipo de
Perchita's team, from
perchita del equipo del
Perchas' team, Los
perchas Los
troncos. The road to Tenerife begins and we're
troncos empieza el camino a tenerife y
not going to do it alone. Papayo will be
no vamos a hacerlo solos papayo estará
supporting Troncas and Troncas with us
apoyando con nosotros a troncos y
during the Play, that is, our Play,
troncas durante la Play o sea aur Play
who doesn't
que no
go out to buy
sale a comprar elan
bread, I think she doesn't eat bread because we have to
pan yo creo que no come pan porque hay
go out and buy it every
que salir a comprarlo cada
day, of course.  you bread is not like let's see
día Claro tú el pan no es como que a ver
if you can buy bread a little less
si puedes comprar pan un poco de menos
quality no I would say but bread at the
calidad no yo diría pero pan a la
bakery of course you don't have to buy it
panadería claro no tienes que comprarlo
every
cada
day and Auron is suddenly going to
día y auron de repente va a ir a
Tenerife to
tenerife a
Tenerife to accompany these people do
tenerife acompañar a esta gente
n't go get carried away Uron Play
no te vayas a enchochado a uron Play
Well whatever he wants like that we have
Bueno a lo que quiera así tenemos luego
content later no No man but let's see of course do
contenido no No hombre pero a ver claro
n't give all your heart ever Auron
no entregues todo tu corazón nunca auron
is very lonely don't give all your
está muy solo no entregues todo tu
heart okay look look look Dj Mario what
corazón vale mira mira mira Dj Mario lo
bu says he won't go to see some player to
bu no irá para ver alguna jugadora a
see but well also Well also Sel
ver pero bueno también Bueno también sel
is very good yes But
está muy bien sí
well also Well also Sarel
Pero bueno también Bueno también sarel
is very
está muy
good many in my place she is she is the
bien muchos en mi pis está está la
pharaoh the pharaoh whatever it is whatever they
faraona la faraona lo que sea lo que sea
call her salt I don't know if here she is also
la llaman sal no sé si aquí también
happy be careful eh For whatever reason she is
contenta cuidado eh Por lo que sea está
happy eh she looks happy normal man
contenta eh se la ve feliz hombre normal
that they have finished first Yes yes for the
que han quedado primeras Sí sí por los
goals I say yes yes good good
goles digo sí
good watch the defenses
sí bien bien bueno ojo las defensas
too eh evis Antonela Mola eh Mario
también eh evis Antonela Mola eh Mario
I know that you There you are going to you are going to sign
Yo sé que tú Ahí vas a vas a fichar
strong well You get good
fuerte bueno Te llevas buenos
fans yes  records to Sara Ismael
aficionados si fichas a Sara Ismael
eh well what do you want me to tell you
eh po yo Qué quieres que te diga
eh Let's see a lot of Caro
eh A ver mucho de Caro
no
no
Well it will be a bite no no
Bueno será un bite no no
Dj Mario is 80% head
Dj Mario es 80% cabeza
20% But why do you put that
20% Pero por qué ponéis eso
poor damn Mario too
pobrecillo [__] d Mario también lo
Cuaron I just remembered do you remember
cuaron me acabo de acordar os acordáis
the cuqueo to Dj Mario the mother who
del cuqueo a Dj Mario la madre que nos
gave birth to us eh the town festivals let's
parió eh las fiestas de los pueblos a
see of
ver
course I don't know it could be a
claro es que no sé podría ser un
bite I want to find myself in that this
bite me quiero enconar en que esta
exclusive is not true I don't want to
exclusiva de no es verdadera no quiero
confirm it No man joking no but let's
confirmarla No hombre broma no pero a
see it's that it surprises me a lot that [ __ ]
ver es que me extraña mucho que [__]
Auron Play has a thing and everyone knows it I don't
que auron Play tiene un rollo y lo sabe
know but yes yes let's go Here they
mundo no sé pero sí sí vamos Aquí lo
are
están insinuando
clearly insinuating it here there is a flirtation no the
claramente aquí hay un coqueteo no la
Girl is letting herself that also
Chica se está dejando que también
putting these things
poniendo estas cosas
eh I say eh I say eh
eh digo yo eh digo yo eh Mientras
Meanwhile gemita
tanto gemita
Meanwhile gemita with the lover over
Mientras tanto gemita con el amante por
there no this is the same
ahí no este es el mismo
path finally the first Snowfall has fallen
camino por fin ha caído la primera
well the first let's see let's see the first
Nevada bueno la primera a ver a ver a
Snowfall I don't know if it is the
ver la primera Nevada no sé si es la
first Snowfall eh it is the same path it
primera Nevada eh es el mismo camino se
looks a lot like but  the fence is missing what
parece mucho pero le falta la valla lo
catches my attention Is that
que me llama la atención Es que le falta
the fence is missing but well maybe it has a piece
la valla pero bueno a lo mejor un trozo
and the other piece does
tiene y otro trozo
n't gemita with her victim it's not a lover that's it it
no gemita con su víctima no es un amante
's a lover
está es un amante
body Yeah well maybe they are a little
cuerpo Sí bueno a lo mejor están algo
wrong because they are already accompanying each other on
mal porque ya se están acompañando en
several trips and in several places But
varios viajes y en varios sitios Pero
well a lover a
bueno un amante un
lover Wi you are not going to spend a euro
amante Wi no te vas a gastar un eurito
to become a member
en hacerte miembro
son the image of gemita was left on the
hijo la imagen de gemita quedó por los
ground let's see but campaigns concentrate
suelos a ver pero campañas concentrar
Asturian dairy no it is not missing
lecher asturiana no le no le faltan
eh Oh
eh
Oh By the way Wait uncle Sur
Ay Ay Por cierto Espera que el tío Sur
put
puso una
something right Now when
cosa justo Ahora cuando estaba
Auron was abduct collagen Auron
auron abduzcan colágeno auron
dicab a kiss
dicab un beso
morons you have seen this
macondas tú habéis visto esto
you scared me eh I [ __ ] in 10 it
tú me ha asustado a mí eh Me cago en 10
scared me let's see it's a
me ha asustado a mí a ver es un click de
23 second click but I [ __ ] in 10 I mean a
23 segundos pero me cago en 10 o sea
soldier
milica
doing a
haciendo un
Stream and they are in the car I understand that it
Stream y van en el coche entiendo que
will be a Stream in I mean I understand that it
será un Stream en o sea entiendo que
will be a moving one no I mean it's not that they
será un en movimiento no O sea no es que
are sitting in the car stopped because they
estén sentado en el coche parado porque
have their seatbelt on and out of the blue it
tienen el cinturón puesto y de buenas a
stops in a
primeras parada en un
traffic light stopped at a traffic light kid it
semáforo parado en un semáforo chaval
was a machine and you think that in
era una máquina y vos te pensas que en
the Stream it's wonderful I don't
el Stream de maravilla yo no te
recommend you Well but you can see how it appears
recomiendo Bueno pero se ve cómo aparece
eh from behind Look, you can see how it appears
eh por atrás Mira se ve como aparece
wait, let's go no, they're not two guys on a
espera vamos a no no son dos tíos en una
motorcycle
moto
eh wait, let's watch the complete clip first
eh espera vamos a ver el clip primero
eh in a machine V you think
completo eh en una máquina V te pensas
about the Stream of wonders I don't
en el Stream de maravillas yo no te
recommend you well
recomiendo a vos bueno
[Music]
[Música]
machine I don't even understand the point of this
máquina no entiendo ni siquiera qué
man I mean, cell phones
sentido tiene esto tío o sea los móviles
today eh almost all cell phones are
a día de hoy eh casi todos los móviles
worthless anymore they're paperweights I mean
lo ya no valen son pisapapeles O sea
Javi that's common with Zlatan but
Javi eso es común en Zlatan pero los
cell phones when they steal them they're paperweights
móviles cuando los roban son pisapapeles
unless they sell them maybe to
a no ser que los vendan a lo mejor para
take it to another country and such they are canceled
llevarlo a otro país y tal se se anulan
by the contract by email they are canceled
por el contrato por el email se anulan
to sell the parts but come on it's not even
para vender las piezas pero vamos ni que
a motorcycle I mean How much are
fuera ni que fuera una moto o sea Cuánto
the parts of a stolen cell phone worth and
valen las piezas de un móvil robado y
What the [ __ ] parts do they buy [ __ ] the
Qué piezas [__] compran [__] a las
motorcycles I remember when kid no eh
motos Yo me acuerdo cuando chaval no eh
that I stole motorcycles I remember
que yo robaba sea las motos yo recuerdo
when  kid no yes you bought
cuando chaval no que sí que te comprabas
one an exhaust your exhaust a I don't know what a I don't
una un escape un tuo escape un no sé qué
know how much no a but but a
un no sé cuánto no una cacha pero pero
mobile what are you selling a screw from the
una un móvil qué vendes un tornillo del
mobile a screen a I don't know what What's
móvil una pantalla un no sé qué Qué vale
that worth is it worth more to you here the brown not of
eso sea te vale más aquí el marrón no de
stealing that even iPhone can be
robar que a hasta iPhone se puede
unlocked, I mean they can they can
desbloquear o sea se pueden se pueden
hack then the phones no and
piratear luego los teléfonos no y los
Unlock them you're missing street Jai if it's
Desbloquea te falta calle Jai si está
deactivated they can assign you another
desactivado pueden asignarte otro
number here almost nobody knows about the
número aquí casi nadie sabe lo del
email code Javi but let's see normally
código email Javi pero a ver normalmente
phones these days they steal my
los teléfonos a día de hoy a mí me roban
phone and I call the
el teléfono y yo lo lo llamo a la
company no or I call Apple in this case
compañía no O llamo Apple en este caso
no this is the email number of the
no este es el número de email del
phone that was stolen and they block it
teléfono que me han robado y lo bloquean
and it's a paperweight no Hi Javi how does it
y es un pisapapeles no Hola Javi que se
feel to have so much member to yourself you
siente tener tanto miembro para ti
've had mine for 7
solito el mío lo tienes desde hace 7
months and you don't use it I love you a kiss Alan
meses y no lo usas te amo un beso Alan
a kiss Thank you very much handsome well we
un beso Muchas gracias guapísimo [__]
already have 50 more eh I'm a
pues ya tenemos 50 más eh soy
technician and everything is
técnico y todo se
unlocked well wow well wow
desbloquea pues vaya tela pues vay tela
but fate you don't imagine that no I mean
sea pero fate tú no imagino que no O sea
Clear I understand that  I don't know, wouldn't they be
Claro entiendo que no se no arían los
two thieves, but they're both on the
dos rateros sino que van los dos en la
motorcycle, they see that there's a person with a
moto ven que hay una persona con un
phone, they don't come from behind and they come and they're
teléfono no vienen por detrás y vienen y
seeing that they have the phone placed there? Of
están viendo que tienen ahí colocado el
course, they won't even imagine
teléfono No claro no se imaginarán ni de
that it's a famous person, they'll
coña que es una persona famosa se
think that it's a person who has
pensará que es una una persona que tiene
the phone placed there for a GPS or
el teléfono colocado ahí para un GPS o
whatever, no, but trust you, to steal a
lo que sea no pero fíate tú por robar un
phone, break a glass you can
teléfono partir un cristal que le puedes
hurt the person who's in the
hacer daño a la persona que está en el
car, you know, I mean, you break a glass
coche sabes o sea tú romper un cristal
so that you cut the person who's in
para que cortes a la persona que está en
the car and you make a big wound there,
el coche y le hagas ahí un una herida
not to you taking a cell phone that you don't
grande no para tú llevarte un móvil que
know if it's good or bad because you
no sabes si está bien si está mal porque
're seeing it from behind quickly, it's not
lo estás viendo desde atrás rápido no es
like I'm saying, wow, what a piece of
como que diga [__] vaya pedazo de
cell phone, you're not seeing it, okay And when you
móvil no lo estás viendo vale Y ya
steal it and when you have it, that's when you
cuando lo robas y cuando lo tienes es
stop to see what phone it is,
cuando te paras a ver qué teléfono es
what model, eh, how much does it cost?
Qué modelo eh cuánto cuesta
Not breaking a car window to do
No romper una ventana de un coche para
this, man,
hacer esto tío
eh Why, for how much, can't you imagine,
eh Para qué para cuánto no s te imaginas
videos of the most famous bed are leaked, [ __ ], [ __ ], I
se filtran vídeos de la cama más famosa
don't think so because they'll
hostias [__] no creo porque ya lo
have already turned it off. Of course, the phone will have already
habrán apagado Claro ya el teléfono lo
been  off But trust you, trust
habrán apagado Pero fíate tú que fíate
you, that F you, eh, I mean, this, eh,
tú que F tú eh o sea esto eh a brunenger
the same thing happened to Brunenger, yeah, my goodness,
también le pasó lo mismo Sí madre mía
latan, no,
latan no
what hunger, you don't know, what fate? Of course,
qué hambre no sabes que fate tú Claro
why is it? You compare, no, you say, damn, you're
porquees tú comparas no tú dices [__]
taking there, I don't know, you're not
te estás llevando ahí yo que sé no te
taking a 4000 gold cord, you don't know, but you
estás llevando un cordón de oro de 4000
're taking
no sabes pero es que te estás llevando
a cell phone that you don't know what
un teléfono móvil que no sabes qué
phone it is, maybe you're
teléfono es que a lo mejor lo estás
seeing it from behind, but then
viendo desde atrás pero pero luego
when you pick it up, it breaks the window and all that
cuando lo coges rompe la ventana y todo
stuff, then maybe it's an
el rollo este luego a lo mejor es un
old cell phone, you know, but apart from that, you
móvil ya viejo sabes pero aparte Tú date
realize that you can go
cuenta que el que puedes ir por aquí
running around here and suddenly someone here looks
corriendo y de repente alguien aquí mira
here, er from next door. Imagine that er
aquí er de al lado Imagínate que er de
next door is a guy who wants to defend himself, to
al lado es un tío que quiere defender a
catch the thief and er from next door and the one
a [__] al ladrón y er de al lado y el
here reacts and opens the door so
de aquí reacciona y abre la puerta para
that you hit the door, boom, okay, or he
que tú te comas la puerta pum vale o te
puts one on you or someone puts you on you, throws you off your
mete un o te mete alguien te tira de la
motorcycle, you know, for a cell phone, dude, for a
moto sabes para un móvil tío para un
cell phone, for a cell phone that you don't even know what cell phone
móvil para un móvil que no sabes ni qué
is,
móvil es
eh, Argentina, coona, fear, what the [ __ ],
eh Argentina coona al miedo qué [__]
what
qué
balls very low budget the
[__] muy bajo presupuesto la
worker tool yes cl those are
herramienta de trabajador sí cl esos son
any I mean it's fake there are people who
cualquier o sea es fake hay gente que
say it's
dice que es
fake it's a follower or someone who
fake es un seguidor o alguien que la
saw it knew what was
veía sabía lo que
going on my first
iba mi primer
irl on the street in
irl en la calle en
Argentina I hope they rob you Haha son of a [ __ ]
Argentina ojalá te roben Ja hijo de [__]
for me it was premeditated Haha maybe something
para mí fue premeditado Jaja capaz se
leaks
filtra
you imagine
algo te imaginas
that you imagine that it's a paper to
que te imaginas que que es un papel para
leak things that they have on their
filtrar cosas que tengan en su
phone Can you imagine
teléfono Te imaginas
and now it starts I mean I don't know milica got
y ahora empiece o sea yo que sé milica
pissed off with Ari for those likes she
se ha [__] con Ari por los likes
gave and says stop you're going to leave entirely and I'm
esos que dio y dice para te vas entera y
going to publish the photos now of your
voy a publicar las fotos ahora de tu
bed of your ex bed that is now my
cama de tu ex cama que ahora es mi
bed n that's true that's it I mean whoever it is to have
cama n eso es verdad ya está o sea el
paid the phone and little
que sea habr pagado el teléfono y poco
else is worth it he mentioned that there are people
más vale mencionó que hay personas con
contacting female streamers with the
contactando a streamer mujeres con la
proposal of writing a book about the
propuesta de escribir un libro sobre las
difficulties of being a woman in the world
dificultades de ser mujer en el mundo
of streaming however she decided to
del streaming sin embargo ella decidió
reject that offer triso chir x25 Hello
rechazar esa oferta triso chir x25 Hola
cpe When you upload content to
cpe Cuando subes contenido a
sk Where to skiwi I don't know what that is dude
sk A dónde a skiwi no sé qué es eso tío
[ __ ] skiwi you can already upload skiwi content
[__] skiwi ya se puede subir contenido
[ __ ] I've seen around  that I have been told
de skiwi [__] he visto por ahí que me
that I already knew it was possible and I
han salido tet de que ya se se podía y
clicked on the App Store but it does
me le di al le di al App Store pero no
n't appear to me no I mean I can't
me no me aparece no O sea yo no me puedo
download the app
descargar la aplicación
no ​​let's see I'm going to
no a ver voy a
try it, it doesn't appear for me yet eh Because
probar a mí no me sale todavía eh Porque
there are people who have it, it doesn't
hay gente que la tiene a mí no me
appear for me It's not that they're talking to me to release a
sale No es que me hablan para sacar un
book about what I want no they don't
libro de hablar de que a mí me da la
want me to talk they want me to
gana no no quieren que hable quieren que
release a book about what it's like to be a
saque un libro de hablar cómo es ser
female streamer and how difficult the
mujer streamer y lo difícil que es el
world of women is on Twitch here there are people
mundo de mujer en Twitch aquí hay gente
who have put me
que me ha puesto
Oh I don't
Ay no lo
see it here there are people who had written to me
veo aquí hay gente que me había escrito
no if they see this I'm 100% sure it
no si esto lo ve estoy 100% seguro de
's bissy do you remember this
que es bissy os acordáis de este
character of
personaje de
bissy before we nominated an anime doll a
bissy antes nominamos a un muñeco anime
moger a
que a un moger que a una
moger a woman I don't understand no the
moger que a una mujer no entiendo no el
anime doll is also a
muñeco anime es también un
man a month ago being a
señor un mes entier siendo una
woman only she writes titles like how
mujer solo ella escribe títulos en plan
hard it is to be a female gamer and
lo duro que ser una mujer Gamer y está
a book is written about how hard it is to be
escrito un libro sobre lo duro que es
a woman no but I don't think that I don't
una mujer no pero yo no creo que yo no
think that it's this t This girl is very
creo que o sea esta t Esta tía es muy
ridiculous the truth is we have live eh And
ridícula la verdad tenemos directos eh Y
these here at the salsería about this
estos aquí en la salsería sobre esta
chick but no I don't understand that on
tipa pero no yo no entiendo eso por
Sel's part what I understand is that by
parte de sel yo lo que entiendo es que
making her write a
haciendo que ella haga un
book Marina amores is not
libro Marina amores no es
[Music]
[Música]
the
la
Ah Marina mor is her name is
Ah Marina mor es ella se llama
Marina I understand that they have offered her to
Marina Yo entiendo que le han ofrecio
write a book another book I mean no no you
que que haga un libro otro libro O sea
know I mean not to
que sabes O sea no que
participate among her latest beauties
participe entre sus últimas lindezas
because there are no female streamers or
porque no hay ninguna mujer streamer ni
anything No but I think that I think that what they have
nada No pero yo creo que yo creo que lo
offered her is for whatever
que le han ofrecido es por cualquier
publisher they have that wants to
editorial que tiene que quiere que
want to put out progressive or
quiere sacar contenido progres o
feminist content or whatever no well they offer her
feminista o lo que sea no pues le ofrece
the topic of her writing it you know a
el tema de que ella lo escriba sabes un
book about selling talking about how
libro de seling hablando sobre lo
difficult it is to be a girl Gamer
difícil que es una ser una chica Gamer
that they talk to me To put out a book about
qué me hablen Para sacar un libro de
talking about what I want no they don't
hablar de que a mí me da la gana no no
want me to talk they want me to put out a
quieren que hable quieren que saque un
book about talking about what it is like to be a female
libro de hablar cómo es ser mujer
streamer and how difficult the world of
streamer y lo difícil que es el mundo de
women is on Twitter do you really think
mujer en Twitter tú de verdad te crees
that I am going to start writing that I
que yo me voy a poner a escribir eso o
mean they want them to write a book about how
sea quiere que escriban un libro de lo
difficult it is and  of the barbarity of
difícil que es y de la barbaridad de
things that I have suffered during these
cosas que yo he sufrido durante estos
years for being a woman obviously I am not going
años por ser mujer obviamente no lo voy
to do it but man I mean I do not
a hacer pero tío o sea es que no lo
understand no I am not going to do it I mean no I am not
entiendo no no lo voy a hacer o sea no
going to do it for me the best
no lo voy a hacer para mí el mejor
streamer in Spain is canecro canecro it is
streamer de España es canecro canecro es
an outrage In fact I do not know why
una barbaridad De hecho yo no sé por qué
canecro has not won the slam of the
canecro no ha ganado el slam de la
career of the year, I mean,
trayectoria del año o sea lo ha ganado
people who I do not understand have won it canecro has been
gente que no entiendo canecro lleva 50
here for 50 years he is alone canecro has not won anything
años aquí él solo canecro no gano nada
because they have not nominated him you know why they have not
porque no lo han nominado sabes por qué
nominated canen because he does not have
no han nominado a canen porque no tiene
an army of 50 rat children from tiktok and
un ejército de 50 niños rata de tiktok y
like him you have an army of 50,000
como el los tienes un ejército de 50,000
rat children from tiktok who campaign
niños rata de tiktok que hagan campañas
for you to vote for you they do not put you in the esl
para que te voten no te ponen en los esl
And that should not be like that I mean if you
Y eso no Debería ser así O sea si tú
are a good streamer you should be nominated
eres buen streamer dees estar nominado
not by Whoever has more rat children on the
no por Quien tenga más niños ratas en
internet that should not be like that by the
internet eso no Debería ser así que por
way this year there is no sl no let's see
cierto es año no hay sl no a ver que le
ask Gema  It's difficult
pregunten a Gema lo difícil que
but let's see Why do they criticize the
es pero a ver Por qué critican las
ham votes? I mean, I criticize
votaciones de los ham o sea yo critico
the ham votes when there's a
las votaciones de los ham cuando hay un
fix but when when it's because Oh it's because there are
tongo pero cuando cuando es por Ay es
more children who vote no but
que tiene más niños que votan no pero
let's
vamos a
see but if it's a content that is from
ver pero si es un contenido que es de
gref which by the way Greg envies the
gref que por cierto que envidia Greg el
other day the video he made with David
otro día el vídeo que hizo con David
Viale I mean he
viale O sea me
put me they cut my arm and atrophy
puso a mí me rajaron el brazo y atrofiar
one
un
the criminals don't care about the
a los delincuentes no les importa la
lives of others Welcome to
vida de los demás Bienvenidos a
Spanish my goodness uncle my goodness well do
españoles madre mía tío madre mía pues
n't see Eh well don't see I almost
no veas Eh pues no veas casi que
prefer that Pedro Sánchez steal from me
prefiero que me robe Pedro
being [ __ ] around organizing my goodness
Sánchez ser jodiendo organizar madre mía
how annoying Ah there are no r os it's that the
qué pesada Ah tampoco hay r os es que el
rwi of last year was a little strange eh the thing with
rwi del año pasado fue un poco raro eh
gre shooting at gemita is that
lo de gre disparando a gemita es que esa
scene I will not erase from my
esca no la borro de mi
head confirmed that there is no has
cabeza confirmado que no hay te ha
confirmed you I mean the ru of
confirmado eso o sea el ru del año
last year was strange eh it was very strange eh Let's see
pasado fue raro eh fue muy raro eh A ver
well it had a lot of dislike I didn't
bueno tuvo mucho dislike Yo tampoco lo
see it so so so so so bad no I mean so so so so so so
vi tan tan tan tan tan mal no O sea tan
so
tan tan tan tan tan tan
bad or so yes I don't know what it seems like
mal o sea sí No saes yo lo que me parece
an outrage to me that they start
una barbaridad que se pongan a
asking for those outrageous amounts of money
pedir esas barbaridades de dinero
rewind Hey, I do have in mind that
rewind Oye yo sí que haí en cuenta hace
like a month and a half ago there is no
como un mes y medio este año no hay
rewind this year no, there won't be one
rewind este año no no va a haber
Apparently eh Someone would have
Aparentemente eh Ya alguien hubiera
said
dicho
something crazy but don't you think it's like a
algo loco pero no creéis que es como un
role that they're playing
papel que están haciendo
[Music]
[Música]
to mislead
para para despistar
Don't you think it's like a role to
No crees que es como un papel para
mislead from the stick Oh someone would have said
despistar del palo Uy ya hubiera dicho
something I don't think they're not that
algo No creo no son tan
smart no I don't know it hasn't been the worst of all how
listos no s no ha sido el peor de todo
hard it is to stay without Dallas eh Javi
qu duro es mantenerse sin Dalas eh Javi
Well yes mar But above all what is no longer
Pues sí mar Pero sobre todo lo que no ya
is to stay as such but above
no es mantenerse como tal sino sobre
all my heart Mark but Mark you
todo mi corazón Mark pero Mark que lo
have written it seven times Calm down
has escrito siete veces Cálmate
Mark Mark
Mark Mark
calm down they do it behind your back Javi
tranquilo lo hacen a tus espaldas Javi
so we don't
para que no
go out to see I think no no to the
salemos a ver yo creo que no no a la
truth I would have I'm going to do a
verdad yo me hubiese voy a hacer un
click of Dallas Mark I'm going to do a clip
click de Dallas Mark voy a hacer un clip
of Dallas I think we would have I think we
de Dallas yo creo que lo hubiéramos yo
would have known eh I think
creo que lo hubiéramos sabido eh yo creo
that at least I would have found out
que yo por lo menos me Hubiera enterado
something
de algo
eh I think we would have found out
eh yo creo que nos hubiéramos enterado
something someone always leaks something
de algo siempre alguien filtra algo la
screw up you know I don't know let's see it's
caga sabes no sé a ver es que estamos a
December 11th debate Dr. Adrian Salama
diciembre debate el doctor Adrián salama
throws out a rather controversial question
lanza una pregunta bastante polémica
regarding the case with Mr. Doctor and Marifer
respecto al caso con Mr doctor y Marifer
Centeno mentions why didn't he not
Centeno menciona que por qué no no
report
denunció
[Laughter]
[Risas]
to
a
Oh when he Why didn't he report d the
Ay cuando le Por qué no denunció a d las
review when he sent him the very delicate
review cuando le mandó el tan delicado
email where you say quite
correo dónde le dices palabras bastante
aggressive words like [ __ ] Pig [ __ ] Looking for
agresiva como [__] Cerda zorra Busca
fame among other insults considered
famas entre otros insultos considerados
as violence what do you
como violencia ustedes qué
think forcing the role eh be very Forza
opinan forzando el rol eh sea muy Forza
very Forza
muy Forza
of let's see this is a friend of Mr. Doctor
de a ver este es amigo de Mr doctor
because he didn't like how things were said to him
porque no le gustó el cómo le dijeron
because he didn't like how
cosas porque no le gustó el cómo le
things were said to him Now I have a
dijeron las cosas Ahora yo tengo una
question When Dallas Mr. Daniel
pregunta Cuando Dallas el señor Daniel
from Spain Dallas review wrote to him the
de España Dallas review Le escribió las
horrific things that I can't even
cosas espantosas que ni siquiera puedo
put here because they would censor me on the
poner aquí porque me censurarían en el
Channel of what he said to him the humiliation that he
Canal de lo que le dijo la vejación que
did to him was Inc quera I mean to me on the
le hizo fue Inc quera O sea me en el
channel and all the
canal y lo comentaron todos los todos
gossip channels commented on it ible Why didn't
los canales de chisme ible Por qué no lo
reported if it was a direct email to
denunció si fue un correo directo hacia
her that is violence I mean he looked for her
ella eso es violencia O sea la buscó
to
para
rape her Why doesn't he get involved with her because she did
violentarla Por qué a él no le nada por
n't get involved with him why against Mr.
no se metió contra él por qué contra Mr
doctor who literally showed that
doctor que literalmente demostró que
she was selling pseudosciences that she
ella estaba vendiendo pseudociencias que
was lying that she was saying
estaba mintiendo que estaba diciendo
things that weren't real that she was
cosas que no eran reales que estaba
putting the health of thousands of people at risk
poniendo en riesgo la salud de miles de
because it comes out nationally
personas porque sale a nivel nacional
saying that if you write with colors
diciendo que si escribes con colores
you can change your
Puedes cambiar tu
life like why I mean why there wouldn't be
vida como por qué O sea por qué ahí no
violence point number one because you are
violencia punto número uno porque te
governed by Spanish laws and
riges por por las leyes españolas y
because you have to make a claim or
porque tienes que hacer una demanda o
an international complaint So I
una denuncia internacional Entonces yo
understand
entiendo
that normally or I mean I haven't
que normalmente o sea yo no yo no he
seen any
visto todavía ninguna
complaint yet I hope one day there will be one so we can
denuncia Ojalá algún día la haya para
find out how it would work I
para enterarnos de cómo funcionaría yo
once wanted to sue an Argentinean and
una vez quise demandar a un argentino y
I and I looked for a lawyer there even
me y me busqué un abogado allí incluso
okay in the end it's not that complicated eh
vale al final tampoco tan complicado eh
When you want to sue someone from
Cuando tú quieres demandar a alguien de
another country well people say I can't
otro país pues la gente dice es que no
sue them because they are from another country
lo puedo demandar porque es de otro país
No no you can sue you can file a
No no tú puedes demandar tú puedes
complaint based on the based on the law
denunciar en base a la en base a la ley
of that country I mean you have to look for
de aquel país O sea te tienes que buscar
a lawyer there and no  I know a solicitor, whatever they
un abogado allí y no sé un procurador lo
ask you, no, but the lawyer told me, let's
que te pidan no pero me dijo el abogado
see. Of course, here you can
es que a ver Es que aquí claro lo puedes
sue, but here in Argentina,
demandar pero aquí en Argentina pues vas
the procedure will take approximately 11 years
a tardar aproximadamente 11 años el
and and and if you win, if you win, the
procedimiento y y y si ganas si ganas la
sentence could be maybe 400, 500
condena podrían ser a lo mejor 400 500
euros, so I said, okay, well, I don't give a [ __ ]
eur entonces dije Vale pues no me cago
about everything, and outside, no, but well, it's the same as,
en todo y fuera no pero bueno es igual
for example, in the United States, in the United
que por ejemplo en Estados Unidos en
States, however, the lawsuits
Estados Unidos sin embargo las demandas
are, like, very large amounts of money, not like, huge
pues son como muy millonarias no como
amounts of money, you see
como muchas cantidades de dinero tú ves
the lawsuits that are filed, not by people on
las demandas que se ponen no la gente de
TV and that's like, I mean, it's a
la tele y eso son como o sea país es
different country, so, of course, Marifer
diferente entonces tú claro Marifer
could sue Dallas, man, she could
podría denunciar a Dallas hombre podría
sue, but under what crime is an
denunciar pero bajo qué delito un
insult? I don't know if in Spain you can
insulto Yo no sé si en España tú puedes
sue for an insult, you can sue,
denunciar por un insulto puedes demandar
but I'll explain now,
pero ahora os explico
okay, sue for insults in Spain, the
vale denunciar por insultos en España la
truth is, I remember that in the past, yes,
verdad yo me acuerdo que antiguamente sí
uh, and maybe it was a sentence of 50 or
eh Y a lo mejor era una condena de 50 o
something like that,
alguna cosa
mm, the crime of slander, it depends on the
mm delito de injuria depende de la
amount, the
cantidad de la de la
severity,
gravedad
harassment, I don't know, it depends, okay, but, of
hostigamiento no sé depende vale pero eh
course, you have to look for it.  life in
claro tienes que buscarte la vida en
another country No but
otro país No pero
but you can't file a complaint for
pero no puedes poner una denuncia por
honor I mean the difference is that
honor O sea la diferencia está en que
one thing is a private email and a and another
una cosa es un email privado y un y otra
thing is a lawsuit
cosa es una demanda
eh For something that you have said in public
eh Por algo que tú has dicho en público
about someone, that is, the right to honor in
de alguien o sea el derecho al honor de
fact
hecho
and it is because you violate the image of
e es porque tú vulner la la imagen de
a person because you damage the image of
una persona porque tú dañes la imagen de
a person then Mr. doctor could be
una persona entonces Mr doctor sí puede
violating Marifer's honor
estar vulnerando el honor de Marifer
okay but of course realize that there in
vale pero claro daros cuenta que allí en
Mexico it is different because there she is not
México es diferente porque allí no está
suing She is reporting or in other words, she
demandando Está denunciando o sea no
is not asking her for anything civilly she is
está pidiéndole nada civilmente lo está
reporting it eh For the issue of
denunciando eh Por el tema de la de de
the insults Okay but she hasn't filed it I mean it
los insultos Vale pero no le ha puesto o
's completely different
sea es que es completamente diferente
here in Spain here in Spain that would
aquí en España aquí en España eso no
have no criminal recourse what
tendría recorrido penalmente lo que ha
Mr. doctor has done zero absolutely zero
hecho Mr doctor cero absolutamente cero
could file a civil lawsuit like the ones you
podría poner una demanda civil como las
have seen here between youtubers no
que habéis visto aquí entre youtubers no
that I have been agonists of some and
que yo he sido agonistas de de algunas y
other gossip channels too well
otros canales de salseo también bueno
a few no longer there are a few but it
unos cuantos ya no ya van unos cuantos
is a civil lawsuit that in the end
e pero es una demanda civil que al final
is asking another person for money because
es pedirle pasta a otra persona porque
oh he owes me money because he has done me  a
ay me debe pasta porque me ha hecho un
damage but what Marifer has done there
daño pero la lo que ha hecho allí
with Mr. doctor here in Spain That is
Marifer con Mr doctor aquí en España Eso
not what crime is that And on top of that
no qué delito es ese Y encima ya
and asking no and debating no if it would
e preguntarse no y debatir no si si
enter into a crime of discrimination
entraría en un delito de discriminación
of course that here in Spain would be a
claro eso aquí en España sería un delito
hate crime but a hate crime here in
de odio pero un delito de odio aquí en
Spain would be eh the victim has to be an
España sería eh la víctima tiene que ser
oppressed minority you see a
una una minoría oprimida ves una
disabled person a well or that he insults her for being a
discapacitada una bueno o que la insulte
woman okay that he treats her badly for being
por mujer vale que la trate mal por ser
a woman Eh or that you insult the a a to
una mujer Eh o que insultes a lo a a a
the immigrants for their race for their
los inmigrantes por su raza por su color
skin color or in other words a hate crime is that
de piel o sea un delito de odio es que
you look down on someone because of
tú menosprecies a alguien por razón de
their religion sexual orientation race
su religión orientación sexual raza
ethnicity
etnia
e woman not gender but but of course
e mujer no género pero pero claro es que
those are not insults for being a woman they
eso no son insultos por ser una mujer
are insults because this doctor
son insultos porque el doctor este se
expresses himself like that with everyone whether he is a man
expresa así con todo el mundo sea hombre
or a woman he already said it no eh Why ca
o sea mujer él ya lo dijo no eh Por qué
n't Marifer report Dallas Well why
Marifer no puede denunciar a Dallas Pues
not because here in Spain you
por qué no porque aquí en España no no
cannot report that or in other words they have
puedes denunciar eso o sea que te han
written you an email insulting you
escrito un email insultándote
if it were repeatedly without you
si fuera de forma reiterada sin que tú
answering anything and there is a person
contestes a nada y está una persona todo
insulting you like that every day  chasing you
los días insultándote así persiguiéndote
and such Well I don't know if maybe a Cos or
y tal Pues no sé si a lo mejor un Cos o
something like that Honestly, I have no [ __ ]
algo por el estilo La verdad ni [__]
idea But what I do have Of course,
idea Pero lo que sí que tengo Claro que
man, it's not the same because here what
hombre no es lo mismo porque aquí lo que
Marifer is claiming is her honor but it's
está reclamando Marifer es su honor pero
all blaming Dallas noo they are
todo culpar a Dallas noo están
comparing the cases but it's out of
comparando los casos pero es por
ignorance it's out of ignorance But that's what I
ignorancia es por ignorancia Pero es lo
'm telling you I mean
que te digo O sea
Javi did you know that Dr. Salama donated
la Javi sabías que el doctor salama donó
to Olivita when she was asking for donations
a olivita cuando ella pedía donaciones
for her Yes yes against Dalas yes yes Hey It's
para su Sí sí contra Dalas sí sí Oye Es
true that girl didn't ask for money to
verdad esa chica no pidió dinero para
report Dallas What happened to all
denunciar a Dallas Qué pasó con todas
those donations And who
esas donaciones Y quién
did Mr. doctor also donated I think in
lo el Mr doctor también donó creo de
fact but what am I telling you I mean
hecho pero qué es lo que te digo O sea
in the end no no no no it's not that it's not a
al final no no no no es que no es un
comparable case Marifer I understand that
caso comparable Marifer Yo entiendo que
in Mexico what she is claiming is her
en México lo que está reclamando es su
honor through criminal means Well here in
honor por la vía penal Bueno aquí en
Spain that wouldn't be the case but what
España eso no sería así pero la lo que
you are claiming is her honor you don't
lo que tú reclamas es su honor tú no
damage the honor of someone you
dañas el honor de alguien a qui
consult in private I mean you Imagine
consultas en privado O sea tú Imagínate
that I have some
que yo tengo unas conversaciones
private conversations where I say that x youtuber is a
privadas donde digo que x youtuber es un
son  of a [ __ ] and one and another and a youtuber
hijo de [__] y una y otro y una youtuber
is a disgusting
es una [__] asquerosa
[ __ ] private [ __ ] you are not damaging her image
[__] privado no estás dañando su imagen
you
me
understand another thing is that you put it
entiendes otra cosa es que tú lo pongas
on Facebook put it in a media
en Facebook lo pongas en un medio lo
put it in a you
pongas en un
know then well there you have the
sabes entonces pues ahí tienes la
main difference equally
principal diferencia igualmente
[Music]
[Música]
one thing is that something is ugly because
una cosa es que una cosa esté fea porque
evidently the email from Dallas Well it
evidentemente el email de Dallas Pues
was very ugly no I mean I remember it very
fue muy feo no O sea yo lo recuerdo muy
ugly but another thing is that it is a crime
feo pero otra cosa es que sea un delito
or something like that that can be
o algo por el estilo que se pueda
reported she had made a
denunciar ella le había hecho una
criticism the criticism is very pathetic
crítica la crítica es muy patética
Also I do not agree at all with
Además yo no estoy nada de acuerdo con
the criticism that she made
la crítica que ella le hizo
but but from there to it being a crime that
pero pero de ahí a que sea un delito
can be reported in Mexico Look at you man I mean it
denunciable en México Fíjate tú tío o
is a country in which for example
sea es un país en el que por ejemplo
we see many things that do not happen and so on
vemos muchas cosas no que pasan y demás
but then nevertheless the laws I do not
pero luego sin embargo las leyes yo no
know if they are harsher or softer there
sé si serán más duras o más blandas allí
or if they have more or less mercy with the
o tendrán más o menos Piedad con los
criminals but nevertheless they condemn
delincuente pero sin embargo condenan
things that are not condemned here Ángel
cosas que aquí no se condenan Ángel
Ortiz A kiss or I do not know if here we are
Ortiz Un beso o no sé si aquí somos más
softer I do not know but it is that here
blandos No lo sé pero es que aquí lo de
yesterday of  mter doctor so the
ayer de mter doctor o sea que que ya el
guy ended up begging for mercy there not
tipo acabó pidiendo ahí clemencia no
picking up the little cable not the one who was going to
recogiendo cablecito no el que iba a
go all the way because he was going to
llegar hasta el final porque se iba a
complicate his life And the thing is that they were going to
complicar la vida Y es que lo iban a
arrest him eh they were going to he was going to look for
arrestar eh lo iban a se iba a buscar la
nonsense for some insults on
tontería por por unos insultos en
YouTube
YouTube
man in Mexico there is no justice Well I don't
tío en México no hay justicia Pues no lo
know the truth but a few of the things
sé la verdad pero unas cuantas de cosas
that we have seen seem a little
que hemos visto me parecen un tanto
strange to me but one thing is clear they
raras pero algo está claro a dala lo
have to report him Yes or yes eh Yes yes if they do
tienen que denunciar Sí o sí eh Sí sí si
n't put him in they won't rest easy
no lo meten no se quedan tranquilo
no but it's as simple Look it's as
no pero es tan sencillo Mira es tan
simple as what the [ __ ] are you going
sencillo como que que qué [__] vas
to what the [ __ ] are you going to report with the
a que qué [__] vas a denunciar con la
law of Mexico to a person who is not
ley de México a una persona que no está
in
en
Mexico As simple as
México Tan sencillo como
that I was freaking out this will be another
eso me quedé flipando esto ya será otro
excerpt okay let's read the thread in
extracto vale vamos a leer el hilo en
another section but I loved this no that
otro trao pero me encantó esto no que
this is something that I would have loved to
esto es una que me hubiera encantado
have for the video What happens is that this
tener para el vídeo Lo que pasa que este
topic doesn't catch me
tema a mí no me pilla
eh I mean this topic is not
eh o sea este tema a mí no me no me está
going well for me the truth is I don't even know if I'll
yendo bien la verdad no sé ni si lo
continue covering it Because the other day
seguiré cubriendo Porque el otro día el
this great video that  I made 26,000
pedazo este de vídeo que hice 26,000
visits and the last one yesterday
visitas y ya el último de de de ayer no
was not this no
fue esto no
14,000 dead tisimo Javi oliveira eh
14.000 muert tisimo Javi oliveira eh
look how good this one was let's see if
fíjate tú qué bien que fue este a ver si
today's works too but dead
el de hoy funciona también pero muert
simo eh oliveira eh
simo eh oliveira eh
26,000 How strange
26.000 Qué raro
but I would have loved to have this no
pero me hubiera encantado tener esto no
Marifer Centeno teaches you a ritual to
Marifer Centeno te enseña un ritual para
avoid legal conflicts we can avoid
evitar conflictos legales podemos evitar
and win the lawsuits and the
y ganar las demandas y las
hearings you need 21 seiva leaves
audiencias necesitas 21 hojas de seiva
blessed oil a white candle a
bendito una vela blanca cerillo de
wooden match and a transparent plate you don't know how many
madera y un plato transparente no sabéis
ladies of telesalseo have done
la de señoras de telesalseo que hicieron
this type of things when when I have
este tipo de cosas cuando cuando yo he
had trials
tenido juicios
javiar no no no they don't do it for me the
javiar no no no no lo hacen por m las
ladies the truth is like they do it
señoras la verdad es como que lo hacen
no
no
[Music]
[Música]
memeo 32 years old
memeo 32 años tiene
Marifer is brief I open Ah the brief of all the
Marifer breve abro Ah lo breve de todas
times that fente has not said
las veces que fente no ha dicho
publicly that she has been threatened and that she
públicamente que la han amenazado y que
has announced that she will take
ha anunciado que emprenderá acciones
legal action however according to her the
legales sin embargo según ella la
complaint against my doctor is the first
denuncia contra mis doctor es la primera
that she has filed in her life is she lying or
que que presenta en su vida miente o
just exaggerating  see many times we
solo exagera a ver muchas veces nos
get heated and say Oh I'm going to report I'm
calentamos y decimos Ay voy a denunciar
going to report and it's happened to me a thousand
voy a denunciar y a mí me ha pasado mil
times I haven't said a thousand reports that
veces no he dicho mil denuncias que
then it gives me when the days go by I'm going to
luego me da cuando pasan los días me a
put myself there would now be a
poner yo habría ahora un proceso
judicial process I'm lazy today in a
judicial Me da pereza hoy en rueda de
press conference Marifer Centeno's lawyers
prensa los abogados de Marifer Centeno
affirmed that Octavio Arroyo better
afirmaron que Octavio Arroyo mejor
known as my doctor committed
conocido por m doctor cometió abuso
sexual abuse against her let's see they say it very
sexual en su contra a ver lo dicen muy
casually but I think it was a let's see
de pasada pero yo creo que fue un a ver
I think they didn't want to accuse her of
yo creo que no quisieron acusar de un
harassment of a sexual abuse what
acoso de una un abuso sexual lo que
they meant to say was like the issue of
quisieron decir era como el tema de por
gender I want to think that they were
género Yo quiero pensar que se
wrong uh that if they did a l
equivocaron eh que si hicieron un l
they are in a live and and such uh I don't think
están en un directo y y tal eh No creo
that because of the face she said sexual abuse or
que por la cara dijera un abuso sexual o
is a person that you have not seen or
sea una persona que no has visto ni
person you understand but on other
persona me entiendes pero en otras
occasions they have said that they have threatened her
ocasiones han dicho que la han amenazado
in
de maneras
strange ways in the past Marifer Centeno has
extrañas en el pasado Marifer Centeno ha
provoked the annoyance of the followers
provocado la molestia de Los Seguidores
of artists and public figures whom she
de artistas y figuras públicas a quienes
has criticized, excusing herself by reading
ha criticado excusándose en la lectura
the face and the interpretation of the
del rostro y la interpretación de la
signature even without having a degree certificate
firma aún sin contar con cédula de grado
or formal certificate  that endorses her for
o certificado formal que la avale para
this
esto
How many times before has she said that she had
Cuántas veces antes ha dicho que había
received threats and that she would proceed
recibido amenazas y que procedería
formally I tell you in September
formalmente les cuento en septiembre de
2021 when she announced that she would not have children
2021 cuando anunció que no tendría hijos
Marifer Centeno announced that every
Marifer Centeno anunció que cada
comment is karma and that through
comentario es un karma y que por medio
social networks she had received
de redes sociales había recibido
death threats for her decision not to
amenazas de muerte por su decisión de no
have children
tener hijos
every comment is karma the last time I
cada comentario es karma última vez que
spoke about the
hablo del
subject I was embarrassed to make this video
tema me generaba pudor hacer este vídeo
of something so intimate but I decided to do it
de algo tan íntimo pero decidí hacerlo
because really in this house it is not an issue
porque de verdad en esta casa no es tema
and I have even received death threats
y hasta amenazas de muerte he recibido
which is
los cuales es una
nonsense in April 2022 she analyzed
tontería en abril del 2022 analizó la
Mona's signature And I don't know who Hero they are
firma de mona Y de Hero no sé quiénes
which provoked the fury of her
son lo que provocó la furia de sus
followers and therefore she announced that she was
seguidores y por ello anunció que estaba
receiving threats however
recibiendo amenazas no obstante más
later this year in July he suggested that
tarde este año en julio sugirió que
Heros had planned the robbery to which
heros había planeado el robo del que
Mona and he were the object
fueron objeto mona y
in 2022 he claimed that some of his videos had been taken down
él en 2022 afirmó que le habían tumbado
on TikTok after claiming
unos vídeos en tiktok después de afirmar
that Carlos Feria was an aggressor who
que Carlos feria era un agresor que
controlled his partner Adri Latina Well
controlaba a su pareja Adri latina Bueno
but Carlos Feria was
pero Carlos feria lo era
eh he got upset and answered her and she
eh é se molestó y le contestó y ella
said of course because  he was an
dijo que pues claro porque era un
aggressor to this day the couple is still together damn
agresor a la fecha la pareja sigue unida
but this thread is a little no I
[__] pero este hilo es un poco no O
mean, I mean, what a fabric eh You have to see and
sea o sea vaya tela eh Hay que ver e
well that is a lie eh if the
pues eso es que es mentira eh si la
couple is still together that is a lie
pareja sigue unida eso es que es mentira
damn see Carlos fera we have videos
[__] ver el Carlos fera tenemos vídeos
eh But well it's not like we have videos
eh Pero bueno no es que tengamos vídeos
talking about this topic there was a video from
hablando de este tema había un vídeo de
the security camera that I think
la cámara de seguridad que yo creo que
the girlfriend leaked in a cry for
lo filtró la novia en un grito de
help not
Socorro no en plan
accidentally okay But there was a video
sin querer vale Pero había un vídeo
where the guy pushed his
donde el tipo le pegaba un empujón a la
girlfriend in front of the girl in front of
a la novia delante de la niña delante de
the girl and sent her flying he sent her
la niña y la mandaba a volar la mandaba
flying boom and hit her against the wall but let's
volando pum y la chocó con la pared pero
go at least a meter and a half he
vamos por lo menos metro y medio la
moves her you have to see Marifer who says that
mueve hay que ver Marifer que dice que
this man is an aggressor
este hombre es un agresor
eh in 2023 was a year full of threats
eh en 2023 fue un año lleno de amenazas
for Marifer Centeno because in that same
para Marifer Centeno pues en ese mismo
year she had controversy that according to her
ao tuvo controversia que según ella
involved threats with Sergio Andrade
involucraban amenazas con Sergio Andrade
Sergio Mayer and No more and no less than
Sergio Mayer y Ni más ni menos que
Yarita and her
yarita y su
essence in May 2023 after years of
esencia en mayo 2023 tras años de
criticizing Sergio  Mayer for his
criticar a Sergio Mayer por su
collaboration in the complaints against
colaboración en las denuncias contra
this Parra Marifer centena stated that
esto Parra Marifer centena afirmó que
analyzing his language he had
analizar el lenguaje de él había
received
recibido amenazas de
death threats but the thread is a bit cheesy in the
muerte pero el hilo es un poco chusta al
end Eh I thought it was something like more
final Eh me creía que era algo como más
No but he's telling me all the times
No pero me está contando todas las veces
that Marifer has said received threats
que Marifer ha dicho recibido amenazas
but of course you weren't denying it I mean I
pero claro no me lo estabas desmintiendo
thought I was going to find
O sea me creía que me iba a encontrar
like look look Marifer here eh she said she was
como mira mira Marifer aquí eh dijo que
going to report and she didn't report no eh look
iba a denunciar y no denunció no eh mira
here she said there were threats but there aren't any
aquí dijo que había amenazas pero no las
What are you doing Why do you put 87 Lili
hay Qué haces Por qué pones 87 Lili que
you made a
te ha
mistake finally A few days ago she
equivocado por último Hace unos días
received a comment where they
recibió un comentario donde la
threatened her this comment she attributed it to
amenazaban este comentario lo atribuyó a
her current fight against my
su actual contienda en contra de mis
doctor but of course that's how it is I
doctor pero claro es que es así yo de
really I mean the people the people who
verdad O sea la gente la gente que
defend my
defiende a mis
doctor man let's see you may be
doctor tío vamos a ver puede tener la
right in the criticism you have made of
razón en la crítica que le ha hecho a
Marifer And what Marifer does
Marifer Y a lo que se dedica Marifer
but neither the ways are good nor the
pero ni las formas son buenas ni ni las
ways are good nor the This is
formas son buenas ni la Esto sí es
hate This is hate that the other one is
hate Esto sí es hate que el otro está
promoting and the other one is taking a
promoviendo y el otro se está dando un
bath of dough  let's go it has already been
baño de masa vamos ya ha
regulated no no but this was
regulado no no pero es que esto fue
true, I mean we saw this and he said that he
verdad o sea esto lo vimos y dijo que
had it in the fi of it was
tenía en la fi de se hiciera en
actually done I consider that the latter
realidad Considero que esta última no
should not go unnoticed however it was
debe pasar inadvertida no obstante fue
done by the social media user Paul to
realizado por el usuario de redes Paul a
whom she should direct her efforts
quien ella debería dirigir sus esfuerzos
and not to my doctor Oh well Okay it was
y no a mis doctor Ah bueno Vale que fue
for
por
Paul let's see I'm
Paul a ver
closing the thread but not without first sharing this
cierro hilo no sin antes compartir esta
beautiful reflection Oh really really
bella reflexión Ay de verdad de verdad
be they look for analogies and they look for things
sea buscan analogías y buscan cosas
where there are none the neurotic this is a
donde no las hay el neurótico esto es un
t by Marifer Centeno and he says the neurotic
t de Marifer Centeno y dice el neurótico
feels that life is a threat and must
siente que la vida es una amenaza y debe
defend himself from that
defenderse de esa
threat like calling her neurotic or
amenaza como llamándola neurótica o
hypocrite or this is like the other day
hipócrita o esto es como el otro día
when they brought out the thing about there were people
cuando sacaron lo de había gente
taking out a tet from where they justified the
sacando un tet de donde justificaba la
word [ __ ] okay By the way, the same ones who
palabra perra vale Por cierto los mismos
later laughed at me in
que que después se rieron de que yo en
court to
el juzgado
justify what it was I don't know if yes [ __ ]
justificara cuál fue no sé si sí zorra
no that she was clever that she is Okay well
no que era astuta que lo es Vale pues
Marifer precisely I know Marifer
Marifer precisamente se Marifer
precisely also said in that video
precisamente también decía en ese vídeo
that [ __ ] is used as an autist and Marifer
que perra se utiliza como auta y Marifer
what that video says It depends on the
lo que dice ese vídeo Es depende el
context or it depends  the whole story and
contexto o depende toda la historia y
what do you know, well, it could be a
qué es lo que sabes pues puede ser una
clever person, of course, I mean, yes, but it
persona astuta claro o sea sí sí pero
depends, but it's how it is, like this, no.
depende pero es como es como esto no O
So, Marifer has posted a thread or an
sea que Marifer ha puesto un hilo o un
article about people who
artículo sobre las personas que se
feel threatened.
sienten amenazadas
Well, and in 2015 she posted a thread about
e Bueno y qué en 2015 puso un hilo sobre
people who feel threatened,
las personas que se sienten amenazadas
but she's referring to
ya pero se está refiriendo a las
people who feel threatened and
personas que se sienten amenazadas y
nobody is threatening them or nobody
nadie las está amenazando ni nadie les
is saying anything to them, or maybe you read
está diciendo nada o a lo mejor lo lees
the article and it means something else. Cos,
el artículo y quiere decir otra cosa Cos
okay, Andy's world explains a lot more
vale el mundo de Andy explica mucho más
about what Marifer is really like.
cosas de cómo es realmente la Marifer
Well, we'll see it tomorrow if you want,
Pues mañana lo vemos si queréis
okay, but it's looking for things to scratch
vale pero son buscar cosas donde rascar
where there aren't any, the truth. I mean, I
donde no las hay la verdad O sea yo yo
think that the case of Marifer and my doctor
creo que el caso de Marifer y mis doctor
was very simple, I mean, it's a guy who
era muy sencillo o sea es un tío que
makes a series of videos that are good, they
hace una serie de vídeos que están bien
don't show a lot, I haven't seen the
no ponen un montón yo no lo he visto los
videos, okay, eh, but I've seen some
vídeos vale eh pero he visto algunos
clips. And well, a criticism that I
clips Y bueno pues una crítica que
understand is well-founded, but
entiendo que está bien fundamentada pero
let's just say, knowing what
vamos ya simplemente Sabiendo a lo que
Marifer does, well, I understand that
se dedica Marifer pues entiendo que la
criticism will be good, but of course, if you
crítica estará bien pero claro si ya
're already doing it with  bad way Hi Javi do
estás haciendo con mala forma Hola Javi
you think Mr. doctor saw any of your
crees que Mr doctor vio alguno de tus
videos for me they are both bad but I
vídeos para mí ambos son malos pero el
dislike the doctor more because of what he did to
doctor me cae peor por lo que le hizo a
Dallas about the father a very guy a very guy a very
Dalas sobre el padre un tío muy un tío
attitude you know I mean very it
muy un actitud muy sabes o sea
causes me rejection it causes me
muy me causa rechazo a mí me causa
rejection but it's not because of Dallas because I
rechazo pero no es por Dallas porque yo
hung out with dla or I talked to Dallas or
me junte con dla o me hable con Dallas o
Ah it's that d no no it causes me rejection
Ah es que d no no que me causa rechazo
in this case it also causes me rejection in
en este caso también me causa rechazo en
this case Marifer and Dallas don't
este caso Marifer y Dallas tampoco se
get along either no they have also fought no
llevan bien no también se han peleado no
but I heard that argument the other
pero ese argumento lo escuché el otro
day also in a click that they sent me it's
día también en un click que me mandaron
not that Javi Well well well well he gets
no es que Javi Bueno pues pues pues pues
involved with Mister doctor because because
se mete con Mister doctor porque porque
Dallas what are you telling me man
Dallas yo que me estás contando tío que
stop basing your [ __ ] life on Dallas
dejes de basar tu [__] vida en Dallas
because Dallas right now is not talking
que Dallas ahora mismo no está hablando
about anything and and you are putting him in
de nada y y lo estáis metiendo en el
this case too I mean let's see if
caso este también o sea vamos a ver si
Marifer also got involved she fought with
Marifer también se metió se peleó con
Dallas no and videos were made and I know and I know
Dallas no y se hicieron vídeos y se y se
well Marifer criticized Dallas but I don't
bueno Marifer criticó a Dallas pero no
remember why it was And then Dallas
me acuerdo por fue Y entonces Dallas le
sent him that email
metió ese email
no I have not even defended the
no yo no he defendido ni siquiera el
email  from Dallas how are you going to defend that
email de Dallas cómo vas a defender ese
email do you understand me
email me
but but no no that my doctor is a
pero pero no no que m doctor es una
person who causes me rejection in this
persona que me causa rechazo en este
subject he is causing me rejection again I mean
tema me está causando rechazo otra vez O
let's see the chick who's
sea vamos a ver la pava que te está
telling you oh you've insulted her Well
diciendo ay que la has insultado Bueno
then that's it well your co says Well then
pues ya está pues tu co dice Bueno pues
look I'm sorry for the insults but my
mira lo siento por los insultos pero mi
criticism is valid okay But the
crítica es válida vale Pero el baño de
mass bath showing up at the door playing
masa presentándose en la puerta jugado
breaking a volleyball for freedom of
rompiendo un voli por la libertad de
[Music]
[Música]
expression and now suddenly no no I'm
expresión y ahora de repente no no yo
going to go all the way I'm not
voy a llegar hasta el final Yo no tengo
afraid of anything even if they put me in
miedo a nada aunque me metan en la
jail until the end I don't have to
cárcel yo hasta el final no tengo que
back down on anything because as I have done it done
recular en nada porque como yo lo he
correctly I don't have to
hecho hecho correctamente no tengo que
apologize for my expressions because they
pedir perdón por mis expresiones porque
are the ones that I use in the
son las que yo utilizo en los
videos man you're calling yourself an aunt
vídeos tío te estás diciendo la tía
[ __ ] I wish I wish all the
[__] Ojalá ojalá fueran todos los
agreements were that easy isn't
acuerdos tan fáciles no te está diciendo
the friend telling you that simply an apology
la colega que simplemente unas disculpas
for the ways and that's it Okay Well then
por las formas y y ya está Vale Bueno
nothing well nothing well nothing I don't
pues pues nada pues nada pues nada no
break the Bing I break I don't know what and now he
rompo el Bing rompo no sé qué y ahora
gets there eh when
llega allí eh cuando ya se ha puesto la
things have gotten serious they were going to arrest him because he
cosa seria que lo iban a detener porque
had  an order apparently not to be able to
tenía una orden por lo visto de no poder
talk about her, which is also
hablar de ella que eso también es una
something that I find impressive. Well,
cosa que me parece impresionante Pues
here in Spain, for them to give you an
aquí en España para que te pongan una
order in which you cannot talk about
orden en la que tú no puedes hablar de
a person, of course, that is a
una persona claro eso es una orden de
restraining order, an order in which you
alejamiento una orden en la que tú no
cannot contact a person or
puedes contactar con una persona ni
talk about
hablar de
them because you have insulted them, which doesn't make
ella porque la hayas insultado que no
sense, no, but well, Mexico,
tiene sentido no pero bueno México
and you go ahead and ignore it, for the hell of it
e y coges y te la saltas por el por por
and on top
las pelotas y encima chuleando Pero
of that, bullying. But still, after the tweet, after yesterday's live where it says, no, no, I want peace, I want peace, I am, I am, I am willing to reach an agreement, I have still seen him on
un acuerdo todavía lo he visto en
Twitter bullying, eh bullying, and
Twitter chuleando eh chuleando Y
saying things with double meanings and
diciendo cosas con dobles sentidos y
so on. I now understand if you don't like someone, they
demás no Ya entendí si alguien te cae
have to go to jail because you don't like them, it does
mal tiene que ir a la cárcel porque te
n't matter if you are right or not, and I have to
cae mal no importa si tienes la razón o
act, go Javi, I am Pambi,
ad di tengo que actuar va Javi soy pambi
what are you talking about, Alejandro, I don't even know what
qué estás hablando Alejandro no sé ni lo
you wrote, nor have you even
que has escrito ni ni ni me has
heard me, who the hell is saying that they have to
escuchado quién [__] está diciendo que
go to jail, my doctor?
tiene que ir la cárcel de mis doctor
How can a person go to jail for
Cómo va ir una persona a la cárcel por
some insults?
unos insultos
idiot I don't like at all the
[__] a mí no me gusta nada la
way he does his content Mister
manera de cómo hace Su contenido Mister
to me he is a person that
a mí es que es una persona que me que me
causes me rejection he causes me rejection I don't know you
causa rechazo me causa rechazo no sé
know but this happens eh I mean It happens he has a
sabes pero esto pasa eh o sea Pasa tiene
lot of fans I mean
mucho fan O sea no le caerá bien
normally people don't like him because he has a
normalmente a la gente porque tiene
lot he has a lot of followers and he moves a
mucho tiene muchos seguidores y mueve
lot and And no and not because of this issue eh I mean he
mucho y Y no y no por este tema eh o sea
has a lot of followers and so on I do believe
tiene muchísimo seguidores y demás yo sí
that now he has doubled his audience
creo que ahora ha Doblado su audiencia
because it was on his Play which also had
porque salía en su Play que también
doubled the audience I
había tenido el doble de audiencia yo
think he has doubled the audience because he
creo que ha Doblado la audiencia porque
has received a lot of support on this issue
ha recibido muchísimo apoyo en este tema
and I think that more than because of him because of how well
y yo creo que más que por él por lo bien
he has done it I think it's because of
que lo haya hecho él yo creo que es por
hatred for
odio a
Marifer you know this one about when Dallas
Marifer sabéis esta de que cuando Dallas
does something it doesn't matter who the enemy is there are
hace algo da igual quién sea el enemigo
certain channels that yes or yes
que Hay ciertos canales que sí o sí se
take the side of the other it doesn't matter eh
ponen de parte del otro da igual eh
Even if they have defended the same thing even if they
Aunque hayan defendido lo mismo aunque
have criticized the same thing from another person
hayan criticado lo mismo de otra persona
when they have been In favor, I mean then the
cuando ha estado A favor o sea entonces
same I think it is it is like out of
pues lo mismo yo creo que es es como por
hatred for Marifer let's not see it is not
odio a Marifer no vamos ver tampoco es
a case Nor for people to put a
un caso Tampoco para ponerse la gente
banner at the door of the play
con pancarta en la puerta del jugad la
freedom  of expression freedom of
libertad de expresión la libertad de
expression but if the guy keeps talking
expresión pero si el tío sigue hablando
and keeps uploading videos who
y sigue subiendo vídeos quién le quién
has cut off his freedom of expression
le ha cortado la libertad de expresión
I [ __ ]
me cago en
10 If it weren't Marif Fer Centeno do you think
10 Si no fuera marif Fer Centeno crees
my doctor would have fared the same well
que a mis doctor le hubiera ido igual
in fact no In fact Mister doctor
pues de hecho no De hecho Mister doctor
has had other problems with other people
ha tenido otros problemas con otra gente
eh Whom he has also
eh A la que a la que también ha
insulted and And no and people haven't messed up
insultado y Y no y no han liado la gente
this
este
chicken without
pollo sin
more
más
guys a huge kiss I love you
chicos un beso enorme os quiero
all
muchísimo
and calling a woman a [ __ ] Traitor
e decir zorra a una mujer Traicionera no
is not an insult it's literal avoiding an
es un insulto es literal evitar un
insult it's like when instead of
insulto es como cuando en vez de
calling No but
llamar No pero
eh me for example the thing is that they
eh yo por ejemplo el tema es que me me
put that cli where I justify the
ponían el cli ese donde yo justifico la
word [ __ ] No no yes literally
palabra zorra No no sí que literalmente
I have a lot of cli where where
Yo tengo un montón de cli donde lo donde
I call myself fox and [ __ ]
yo me llamo a mí mismo zorro y zorra
friends of mine here I mean what fox are you no I
amigas mías aquí o sea qué zorro eres no
mean all my [ __ ] life Aha now you
O sea de toda la [__] vida Aha ya tú le
can give it the context that you want to
puedes dar el contexto que tú le quieras
give it obviously it will
dar evidentemente
depend on the community it's true and let's
dependerá la comunidad es verdad y vamos
see the community s it's
a ver la comunidad s es
true how long has it been since I entered
verdad cuánto tiempo llevo sin entrar en
that  lion den eh how long has it been since I
esa leonera eh cuánto tiempo llevo yo
entered this
sin entrar en esta
lion den wizard this week with the
leonera wizar esta semana con los
membership gifts poor thing eh poor
regalos de membresía pobrecillo eh pobre
sete poor thing
sete pobrecillo
eh look at this wonder of Javi oliveira
eh vean esta maravilla de Javi oliveira
wasa
erala
beautiful There are always two a master and one
bonito Siempre son dos un maestro y un
learned not one more not one less but
aprendí ni uno más ni uno menos pero
these people are still in Li with
esta gente todavía sigue en Li con
us no I mean from the ler I saw the other day
nosotros no O sea del ler vi el otro día
a move by this lady I don't know about this
una movida de la señora no sé de la
lady the last thing I saw was supporting
señora lo último que vi fue apoyando lo
Tania's thing man supporting
de Tania tío apoyando lo de
Tania's thing Megan Fox andun Kelly Ah they've
Tania Megan Fox andun Kelly Ah que han
broken up [ __ ] what breakups this this year no
roto [__] qu rupturas este este año no
Sebastian
la Sebastian
would be a member of the youth Sebastian
ería miembro de la chavalería Sebastián
with VPN from
con VPN de
[Laughs]
[Risas]
Yugoslavia let's see
yugoslavia a ver
2520 but
2520 pero
I said [ __ ] but a lot of text no the video
dije [__] pero mucho texto no el vídeo
no
no
252 wants to
252 quiere
see I have my girlfriend next to me and she defends
ver tengo a mi novia al lado y defiende
the doctor what should I do do I agree with her
al doctor qué debería hacer le doy la
or sleep on the couch Haha greetings
razón o duermo en el sillón Jaja saludos
from Virginia Mexico leave her leave her
desde Virginia México déjala déjala
don't be so much your girlfriend because with
tampoco para tanto tu novia porque con
all this now when I have to
todo esto yo ahora a la que me tenga que
do a reform or something I'm capable of
hacer una reforma o algo soy capaz de
putting myself with a tutorial  from
ponerme yo mismo con un tutorial del
bricomanía Before calling a
bricomanía Antes que llamar a una
company I swear they've got me
empresa te lo juro que me tienen
scared well and speaking of scared
acojonado bueno y hablando de acojonas
It's that yesterday I received a message from a
Es que ayer recibí un mensaje de de una
follower that I'm going to put it
seguidora que os lo voy a poner por
here
aquí
and Between that and some things
y Entre eso y algunas cosas
that they've been telling me or or I've been
que me han ido contando o o he ido
sharing of course it's made me
compartiendo claro me ha hecho como
reflect a little bit that it's very easy for
reflexionar un poco que es muy fácil
me to be recording in my house about a topic
estar yo grabando en mi casa de un tema
because I hope it never happens but I see you with
porque ojal nunca suceda pero te veo con
all the ladies by your side entering
todas las señoras a tu lado entrando a
a trial what's more I see them more brave to the
un juicio es más las veo más bravas a la
lady eria Hey next year I have
señor eria Oye el año que viene tengo
one eh next year I have a
uno yo eh el año que viene tengo un
trial I don't know if it's in January February
juicio no sé si es en enero febrero
March around there that was the thing but we could
marzo por ahí era la cosa pero podríamos
summon the
convocar a la
mass gentlemen to my doctors eh What
señoreros de masa a los mis doctor eh Lo
happens is that I think I'm not going it's not
que pasa que yo creo que no voy no es
true I'm not going to that trial I'm not going
verdad yo no voy ese juicio Yo no voy va
to a forum member they take a forum member as a
a una forera llevan a una forera de
witness let's get things clear
testigo vamos a a dejar las cosas claras
eh I've been talking about an issue
eh yo he estado hablando de un tema
regarding this these last two
respecto a esto est los últimos dos
videos that I've uploaded to the Channel about a topic
vídeos que he subido al Canal de un tema
that is public with information that is
que es público con informaciones que son
public  I want to tell you that at the
públicas quiero decirte que al fin y al
end of the day I have the right to create content
cabo tengo mi derecho a crear contenido
about things that are public, giving my
sobre cosas que son públicas dando mi
opinion, exercising my right to
opinión ejerciendo mi derecho a la
opinion and commenting on what has
opinión y y comentando lo que ha
happened, not in the same way that it has
sucedido no de la misma forma que lo ha
taken so long, like ABC has done, like
hecho tardear que lo ha hecho el ABC que
El Confidencial has done, like so
lo ha hecho el confidencial que lo han
many media outlets have done, no,
hecho tant medios de comunicación no
but it is true
aá pero sí es cierto
[Music]
[Música]
that of course no, no, you're not
que claro no no estás no estamos
talking about normal people, we're
hablando de gente normal estamos
talking about a person who has accumulated
hablando de una persona que acumulaba
quite a few crimes and serious ones, so we're not talking
bastantes delitos y y graves entonces no
about a person who,
estamos hablando de una persona que
well, that gives me the creeps, I do
bueno que me da
n't know, maybe I'm
cosa no sé es que igual estoy
dramatizing a little bit the possible
dramatizando un poco las las posibles
consequences or or I don't know what that maybe I know, I
consecuencias o o no sé que que
mean, I've been creating
que igual se o sea he estado creando
content this week a little
esta semana como el contenido un poco
without thinking, like, wow, this has happened, I've
sin pensar rollo ostras ha pasado esto
gathered information and I'll tell you about it, but I have
recopi información y os lo cuento pero
n't reflected and I haven't thought a
no he reflexionado y no he pensado un
little bit beyond, like,
poquito más allá
something could happen to me
de Me podría llegar a pasar algo
or I don't know, it's just that I don't know how to focus, it's
o no lo sé es que no sé cómo enfocar es
that in the end, on TV when
que lo al final la tele cuando hablan
people talk about things, not
una gente que hacen cosas no gente
bad people, you think about this a lot, eh,
chunga esto lo pensaris muchas veces eh
eh, when they talk about bad people or people
eh Cuando hablan de gente chunga o gente
like that. No, that  have a special soon or
así No Que tenga un pronto especial o lo
whatever, it's not clear they see it like TV is TV
que sea no claro lo ven como la tele son
TV, of course TV is an entity
la tele la tele claro la tele es un ente
of people that you don't know who they are, you
de gente que no sabes quiénes son no les
don't put faces to them, you don't know who the boss is, no, you don't
pones caras no sabes quién es el jefe no
know who's in charge Who has
no sabes quién es el que manda Quién ha
decided on that content and well, the
decidido ese contenido y bueno los
collaborators, the presenters who
colaboradores los presentadores que
are there are people who are working
están ahí son gente que están trabajando
Not clear but well This happens there are not
No claro pero bueno Esto pasa no hay
many people who understand it and people who do
mucha gente que lo entiende y gente que
n't, well anyway, my contribution to the community,
no bueno en fin mi aporte a la comunidad
ole
ole
p sex sex sex sex sex sex sex sex
p sex sex sex sex
sexal the other day I was watching a
sexal el otro día estaba viendo como una
jeeva approach me Aba the other day I
jeeva se me acercaba Aba el otro día
was watching a jeeva
estaba viendo como una jeeva se me
approach me, devil, ma she's got a real
acercaba [__] ma estáa tiene una bien
[ __ ] I don't know what I'm going to do, I want to
cabrona Yo no sé qué voy a hacer quiero
give her anal sex sex sex sex sex
darle sexo anal sexo sexo sex sex se
something else has been said Ricky hasn't
ha dicho algo más Ricky del tema no ha
said anything else about the subject,
dicho más nada
not this
No este
guy, nobody, the kids, after making
tío nadie la chavalería después de hacer
mine in less than two days and having fewer live
mios en menos de dos días y tener menos
broadcasts and videos than the rest of
directos y vídeos que el resto de los
Javil Veira's channels And still having to
canales de javil veira Y todavía tener
wait for the
que esperar a que se digne a aparecer el
gentleman from in 10 minutes I'll be there to deign to appear and
señor de en 10 minutos estoy ahí y
apart from that  already left the
aparte que ya abandonó la
community [ __ ] you
comunidad Vete a la [__]
wale the family is about to
wale la familia está por
grow
crecer
How if it's a boy pan if it's a girl bis I
Cómo si es niño pan si es niña bis
would have liked to see the lord this of
me hubiera gustado ver el lores este de
del gibel with the canine that has
del gibel con el canino que se ha
fought again now but this man
peleado ahora otra vez pero este señor
is a liar he says I have no words and
es un mentiroso dice no tengo palabras y
his t is like
su t tiene como
25 it ends direct and the
25 termina directo y la
goat gives away two twice 50 members I
cabra regala dos dos veces 50 miembros O
mean yesterday when we cut the live is it
sea ayer cuando cortamos el directo es
true they told me by md when we
verdad me lo dijeron por md cuando
cut the live Sebastian gave away 100
cortamos el directo Sebastián regaló 100
more members he didn't give a
miembros más le sudó toda la
damn he didn't give a damn his
[__] le sudó toda la [__] su
life gibel was always a crab eh
vida gibel siempre fue cangrejo eh
Although you want to although you want to
Aunque se quiere aunque se quiere
take it long he finally realized
tardar al fin se dio cuenta
Look javiel canine against
Mira javiel canino contra
gibel
gibel
therapy the salsería
terapia la salsería
when you go to brag to the gentlemen
cuando vas a presumirle a la señoreros
3000 members in the salsería and they even
3000 miembros en la salsería y hasta te
give you a member in telesalseo
regalan miembro en telesalseo
no no no we are
no no no somos
eh 4500 eh
eh 4500 eh
member Javi has the haters like that but
miembro Javi tiene a los hater así pero
always Javi one of these days
siempre Javi uno de estos días
Ah look it's true they have the trial José
Ah mira es verdad tienen el juicio José
Manuel López has has the trial this
Manuel López tiene tiene el juicio este
when did he say  this Thursday I
cuándo dijo este jueves o
mean tomorrow not tomorrow is
sea mañana no mañana es
Wednesday the day after tomorrow is Thursday
miércoles pasado mañana tiene el jueves
eh Let's see what happens man because there's going to
eh A ver qué pasa tío porque va a abrir
open a melon in justice
un va a abrir un melón en la justicia
this eh I don't know if there has been any other
esto eh yo no sé si ha habido algún otro
case in which the center has been held civilly
caso en el que civilmente el centro se
responsible for something like this I mean eh watch out
haya hecho responsable de algo así O sea
eh watch out because if José
eh ojo eh ojo porque si lo gana José
Manuel wins I hope it's worth it because it's amazing
Manuel Ojalá vale porque es una pasada
As these issues often happen in
Como pasan muchas veces estos temas en
institutes and schools m are going to
los institutos y los colegios m se van a
get their act together they're going to get their act together
poner las pilotas se van a poner las pil
and I'm glad because obviously I have
y me alegro porque evidentemente tengo
children and I'm
niños y me
glad I'm glad I'm very scared of
alegro me alegro A mí me da mucho miedo
the issue of bullying and everything else it scares me a lot
el tema del bullying y demás me da mucho
having children eh that it happens to a
miedo teniendo niños eh que le toque un
son of a [ __ ] from a family that you don't know
hijo de [__] de una familia que no sabes
can
puede
perfectly well fall into a class where there's
perfectamente puede caer en una clase de
a family that that that that
que haya una familia que que que que que
likes that the child misbehaves that
le guste que el niño se porte mal que
the education of their children passes you
pase la educación de sus hijos me
understand we saw this yesterday on TV
entiendes esto lo vimos ayer en la tele
this today eh And generally nothing happens here
este hoy eh Y Generalmente aquí no pasa
people have to criticize and Generally
nada la gente ha criticar y Generalmente
here Oh Sorry sorry friend Sorry I
aquí Ay Perdona perdona amigo Perdona
wasn't watching Generally the
que no te estaba viendo Generalmente las
criticism comes from the  Ignorance and
críticas vienen desde la ignorancia y la
people don't know you like you know yourself,
gente no te conoce como tú te conoces
so you know who you are and you
entonces tú sabes quién eres y escuchas
only listen to the people who also tell you
solora a la gente que también te dice
nice things. I liked that. I liked
cosas bonitas eso me gustó eso me gustó
that. My
eso
dear. But what a good vibe
querido pero pero qué buen rollo siempre
Aaron always has, eh, I mean,
tiene el Aarón eh o sea el
Aaron, except for that video we saw. No, what he
Aarón menos el vídeo aquel que vimos no
did, no, eh, what. What a good vibe he
que hizo no eh qué Qué buen rollo
always has. What a charming child, right? He's
siempre tiene qué Encanto de niño verdad
handsome, on
sea encima es guapo
top of that, everyone likes him. He doesn't think
encima le cae bien a todo el mundo él no
anyone dislikes him. You know, the other day
le parece mal nadie Sabes el otro día
when he had to respond to that, he
cuando tuvo que responder a eso lo
responded with all the politeness in the
respondió con toda la educación del
world. You know, it's just that he lives, lives
mundo sabes es que es que vive vive
super chill, lives really chill,
super chill vive chill de [__]
eh, the little team, the little team.
eh el equipito el equipito
No, don't overdo it, don't overdo it, don't
no no se pasen no se pasen no se
overdo it,
pasen
pambi panis, kids. When we have to
pambi panis chavalería Cuando tenemos
spend another day without a live show from
que pasar otro día sin directo del
Grandpa. There comes a time when you
abuelo Ya lga un momento en que usted
say let what has to flow, let it flow and let what has to go, and that's it.
dice que fluya lo que tenga que fluy y
[Laughter]
[Risas]
And years laughing that Dala could go to
y años riéndose de que dala podría ir a
jail. Yes, yes, good exclusive the
la cárcel Sí sí buena exclusiva la del
other day, eh, good exclusive, eh. Javi was in his
otro día eh buena exclusiv eh Javi en su
time.  well diesel with
época era bien diesel con
hair Hey I want you to make more memes
pelo Oye quiero que me hagáis más memes
of this eh because I find
de esto eh que me hace mucha gracia
these things very funny eh from gibel's drawings It's
estas cosas eh de los dibujitos de gibel
that the kids are
Es que la la chavalería somos
barbarians man my goodness 100 members The
bárbaros tío madre mía 100 miembros Los
Sebastians Jai
Sebastianes Jai
[Laughs]
[Risas]
oliveira the kids with Sebastian
oliveira la chavalería con Sebastián
breaking records after seeing Javi
rompiendo récords después de ver a Javi
calling us stiff No no but of course
llamándonos tiesos No no pero claro es
apart from the record It hasn't been
que aparte el récord Todavía no se ha
surpassed yet eh the record stood at 5500 and
superado eh el récord se quedó en 5500 y
something around there eh at 5500 and something eh
pico por ahí eh en 5500 y pico eh se
the
quedó el
record stood the record would be reaching 6
récord el récord ya sería llegar a los 6
7000 members eh [ __ ] But that must be
7000 miembros eh [__] Pero eso sera de
[ __ ] crazy
[__] locos
No yes it's true man it's
No sí que es verdad tío
noticeable yes it's true that it's not
nota sí que es verdad que no es
now you're invoking it no no no no let's
ahora lo estás invocando no no no no a
see it would be cool but what I like is
ver molaría pero a mí lo que me gusta es
that each person contributes a little bit not
que cada persona aporte un poquito no
that a guy comes and gives you 2000
que venga un tío y te regale 2000
members but that each person is there are
miembros sino que cada persona sea hay
100 people here because one out of five
aquí 100 personas porque uno de cinco
another  10 another cco another one you know but what
otro 10 otro cco otro uno sabes pero que
about all one It gives me the creeps many times
lo de todo uno Me da cosa muchas veces
dude it gives you pure I don't reject it okay but
tío te da puro no lo rechazo vale pero
[ __ ] the thing is that they do it you know fi
[__] lo suyo es que lo hagan sabes fí tú
at this point they are celebrating
a estas alturas están celebrando
600 we are the
600 somos los
joints a video of Javi Bea in his
porros se filtra vídeo de Javi Bea en su
youth is leaked Hi, I'm El Cejas and today I'm going to
juventud Hola soy El Cejas y hoy os voy
show you a compilation of all my
a enseñar una recopilación de todos mis
master strokes to win a fight very
golpes maestros para ganar una pelea muy
easily the first the
fácilmente el primero la patadita del
tiger kick you move your foot like this and when he's
tigre le mueves así el pie y cuando esté
distracted hit him all over the face he's going to
distraído le pl en toda la cara se va a
fall to the ground round
caer al suelo redondo
second hit the bullía kick you
segundo golpe la patada del bullía le
grab him like this you put it like this in his whole
coges así le metes así en todo el
chest that he's going to fall round to the
pechamen que se va caer redondo para el
ground What happened to seja dude I mean El
suelo Qué fue del seja tío O sea ya El
seja Well I think he still appears in
seja Bueno creo que aparece todavía en
some Santiago movie for sure No
alguna película de Santiago segura No
but little more will not remain the brain F
pero poco más no va a quedar el cereb F
you eh seja was a turkey who came to
tú eh el seja fue un pavo que llegó a
charge
cobrar
15,000 euros for promoting potato chips
15000 eur por promocionar patatas fritas
in an Instagram post but
en una publicación de Instagram pero es
these types of things are temporary
que este tipo de cosas son temporales
per
per
howled And if you see that with your legs
aullado Y si ves que con las piernas no
you are not very agile it will not go  well very easy
eres muy ágil no te va bien muy fácil
also you go up to him and you say Hey
también te lo acercas y le dices Oye
little pigeon
pichonzuelo
little pigeon take it easy because today I didn't
pichonzuelo tranquilito porque hoy no he
come in the mood for a fight you grab him like this you headbutt him his
venido con ganas de pelea le coges así
torch is going to be broken
le pegas un cabezazo se le va a quedar
and if he
la tocha partida y si se te pone tonto
gets stupid you hit him with an elbow at 100 and if not at 101 So careful it was funny man it was funny to me there are things that are true things that aren't so much but well it was funny my mom and those gossip that you look What do they contribute to your
esos salseos que miras Qué aportan en tu
life
vida
Nothing also factor
Nada también factor
eh 100 people and only two
eh 100 personas y solo dos
Live factor total
Live factor total
eh everyone hates you
eh todos te odian
Wow but I love you
Wow pero yo te amo
Oh this t really I loved it a lot
Ay este t de verdad Me encantó muchísimo
eh I mean when
eh o sea cuando
I'm here this is that I'm fighting with the
me este est que me estoy peleando con el
boxing guy with Bertrán in Dongo Mondongo
de box con el bertrán en dongo mondongo
this one and and I say dude you're the first black guy I
este y y digo tío eres el primer negro
've ever met he was picking on a girl
conozco se estaba metiendo con una chica
for being fat and I say dude you're the
por estar gorda y le digo tío eres el
first black guy I've ever met that looks 20
primer negro que conozco que aparenta 20
years older than he is here you are to
años más de los que tiene estás tú para
talk about anyone's physique You know that this
hablar el físico de nadie Sabes que este
turkey is 5 years younger than me, I mean he's from the
pavo tiene 5 años menos que yo o sea es
90s, eh And he took his best photo, this
del 90 eh Y ha cogido su mejor foto esto
is the apya no senpai Thank you very much,
es la apya no senpai muchas gracias
welcome handsome, okay And then
bienvenido guapo vale Y entonces se hizo
Canon made this clip,
Canon este clip
dude, black, I don't agree with you,
tío negro no estoy de acuerdo contigo
dude, I don't agree
negro no estoy de acuerdo
with you, it seems like a fantasy to me
contigo me parece una fantasía
because we haven't had a live show
yo porque llevamos dos días sin directo
from the gasan, dude But this is often a
de los gasan tío Pero esto muchas veces
lie, eh, words can't
es mentira eh palabras no pueden
describe how happy I am right now,
describir lo feliz que estoy ahora mismo
but numbers, yes, zero out of
pero los números sí cero de
10 words, no Jan planas and his disciple
10 palabras no Jan planas y su discípula
Tania de tierra
Tania de tierra
tean trepa Oh, but well, this is no longer
tean trepa Ay pero bueno este ya no es
the trepa team, eh, I mean, trepa and his
el team trepa eh o sea la trepa y el
son have already been dismissed from here, eh, they've been
hijo han sido ya desvinculado de aquí eh
fired,
han sido despedidos
eh Hey, Dallas is super missing, no I mean, he
eh Oye el Dallas está super desaparecido
uploads videos of his songs,
no O sea sube sus vídeos de sus temas
but he's not really absent Why hadn't I
pero no está como muy ausente Por qué no
seen this until now that Roman
había visto esto hasta ahora que Roman
is prettier
se má lindo
[Laughs]
[Risas]
How disgusting you are, dude Javi in ​​Spain, where
qué asco dais tío Javi en España dónde
are my colleagues Javi in ​​Korea, seo of
están mis colegas Javi en Corea seo de
a multinational K-drama actor and
uno multinacional actor de K dramas y
BTS choreographer, then who is not traumatized with  Javi
bts luego que no está traumado con Javi
dude seriously dude seriously this guy
tío en serio tío en serio este señor
well they already sent me eh that he made a
bueno ya me mandaron eh que hizo un
video I mean I trust you I'm glad he
vídeo o sea yo fíate tú me alegro que
takes another arm let's see if it's true and he
coja otro brazo a ver si es verdad y lo
hooks it and doesn't let go no eh it's going
engancha y no lo suelta no eh que le va
very well for him messing with Marifer now and what he
muy bien metidos con Marifer ahora y que
has he had a video of 100,000 views
tiene tuvo un vídeo de 100,000 visitas
not a hundred and something thousand views and the
no ciento y pico mil visitas y el
beginning of the video is Javi
principio del vídeo es Javi
Oliveira the beginning of the video is Javi
oliveira el principio del vídeo es Javi
Oliveira what the [ __ ] do I have to see well
oliveira qué [__] tengo que ver yo bueno
and they sent me a clip of him defending
y me mandaron clip de él defendiendo a
Mr. Doctor No no freedom of expression
Mr doctor No no la libertad de expresión
No look at this tweet Marifer says that
No mira en este tweet Marifer dice que
[ __ ] is smart and now she's getting the tip dude dude dude I
perra es astuta y ahora coge el tip tío
mean he's using that he's doing
tío tío o sea está utilizando que le va
well a topic to throw [ __ ] at
vaya bien un tema para tirarme [__] a
me it's like I have nothing to do with
mí es como que no tengo nada que ver en
this topic mate it's not tremendous tremendous
este tema colega no es tremendo tremendo
tremendous Oh But well it will be little by little it
tremendo Ay Pero bueno será poco a poco
will be a matter of time then it will go
será cuestión de tiempo ahí ya se irá
Goodbye Mister doctor You'll do better in the
Adiós Mister doctor Te irá mejor en el
boat Oy why do you
bote Oy el para
masturbate your mind ejaculate your ideas
qué masturba tu mente yacula tus ideas
Oh we had we had something from Ricky eh we had
Ay teníamos teníamos algo de Ricky eh
something from the  Ali del Ali Okay but I'm
teníamos algo del Ali del Ali Bueno pero
going to put it in a tweet better I'm
lo voy a poner un twit mejor
going to put it in a tweet better guys
lo voy a poner en un twit mejor chicos
I'm going eh I have a dream that you don't see
me voy eh que tengo un sueño que no veas
man I have the bad boy and he
tío tengo al chico malo y me
[Music]
[Música]
wakes me up and he's going to wake me up tomorrow
despierta y me va a despertar mañana por
morning and tomorrow I have to do
la mañana y mañana tengo que hacer
tomorrow I'm going to be busy I don't know what
mañana voy a estar liado no sé qué
appearances I'll make tomorrow eh Well I have
apariciones haré mañana eh Bueno tengo
with Marina telesalseo 100% I don't know what
con Marina telesalseo 100% no sé qué
appearances I'll make tomorrow
apariciones haré mañana
because I have tomorrow I have to sell a
porque tengo mañana tengo que vender un
car a car not Lorena's car that I
coche un coche no el coche de Lorena que
bought her a car and no it and no no no he doesn't want he doesn't want to have a
le compré un coche y no lo y no que no
car he doesn't want to drive it he doesn't
coche que no quiere conducirlo que no
want
quiere
anything after 3000 members like this he
nada después de 3000 miembros así nos
thanks us what's up I would stay here until
agradece qué va yo me quedaba aquí hasta
5 or 6 in the morning and I would have opened
las 5 o 6 de la mañana y hubiese abierto
today exclusively for the salsa bar for 5
hoy en en exclusiva para la salsería a 5
hours but the
horas pero es que tampoco tampoco nos
salsa people are not accompanying us either but yes I
están acompañando los salseos pero sí
promise you that I am preparing
que os prometo que estoy preparando una
something beautiful beautiful beautiful
cosita guapa guapa
yes I promise you that I am
guapa sí que os prometo que estoy
preparing something beautiful beautiful beautiful
preparando una cosita guapa guapa guapa
for you for the  main channel
para ustedes para el canal principal
trust me
confiar en mí
give me give me give me give me
dme dme dme dme
eh 15 days Yes more or less in a couple
eh 15 días Sí más o menos en en un par
of weeks ask me Javi you
de semanas preguntarme Javi nos
promised us something what happened okay maybe
Prometiste algo qué ha pasado vale por
in 15 days or so I'll be
ahí dentro de 15 días más o menos lo
able to
podré
say I'm doing
decir estoy haciendo una
something I trust trust me a kiss handsome
cosa confío confiar en mí un beso guapos
Hey go to the main Channel there's a
Oye iros al Canal principal que hay un
video okay go to the main Channel and
videíto vale iros al Canal principal y
support the video a kiss put
Apoyar el videíto un beso poner
comments of yours okay I
comentarios de los vuestros vale que he
saw that yesterday's video was filled with
visto que el vídeo de ayer se llenó de
comments from these handsome guys
comentarios de estos guapos de ustedes
okay kiss I love you damn you are the
vale beso os quiero [__] [__] sois los
best sons of [ __ ] the best community
mejores hijos de [__] la mejor comunidad
on the internet both in gentlemen
de internet tanto en señoreros